<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[outsourcing-it-support-services]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[10 Factors to Consider when Outsourcing IT Support Services]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[10-factors-to-consider-when-outsourcing-it-support-services]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60fbb]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 17 2023 10:56:48 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 08:26:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Outsourced IT Services | 10 Factors to Consider | TechVertu]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Outsourcing IT support is a great way to help your business running. here are 10 things to keep in mind when considering outsourcing IT support services. ]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[52]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>&zwj;<strong>Outsourced IT support</strong>could be a critical aspect of a company's infrastructure. Without efficient, reliable, and consistent IT performance, a large majority of organisations would not be able to function. In this article, we will discuss factors you should consider when outsourcing <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/it-support">IT support service</a>.</p><h2>What is outsourced IT support?</h2><p>For some companies having a permanent department to manage business needs is not always possible; therefore, most companies consider outsourcing to a team of IT support professionals. This option can save money, safeguard against cybercrime, and offer broadband and security solutions while offering specialist advice to promote economic growth.</p><h2>Ten things to remember while outsourcing IT support services</h2><p>Outsourcing IT support can be a great way to help your business stay up and running, but before making a decision, there are some important things to remember. Here are the top 10 things to keep in mind when considering outsourcing IT support services:</p><h3>Reduced costs</h3><p>The financial benefits of outsourcing to <a href="https://www.techtarget.com/searchitchannel/definition/managed-service-provider">managed service providers (MSP)</a>create substantial economic benefits for businesses in several areas.</p><p>The cost of an internal IT workforce and equipment and software upgrades could severely impact time and resources, preventing a team from tackling more urgent projects. Outsourcing IT support services will save considerable time and money on employing staff and purchasing equipment.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/63c6a3d5c99383e62bc6c2db_money-saving-piggybank.webp"></div></figure><h3>Account management</h3><p>Account Managers are committed to clients and are knowledgeable about their business operations and requirements. For larger companies, this is vital, as they have one point of contact with someone who knows their business well and with whom they have built a relationship.</p><p>An account manager offers a seamless service, often making it their priority to rectify issues immediately, maintaining professional, reliable assistance.</p><h3>Location</h3><p>While many IT support companies work remotely and numerous IT issues can be solved this way, it should not always be the only option. When it comes to upgrades and physical IT issues, a specialist visiting the office is a necessity.</p><p>It is also worth considering the&nbsp;advantages of employing a local IT support team, as new equipment, security camera upgrades, and broadband installation all call for on-site visits, which can incur unnecessary travel costs and additional charges.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/63c6a44794ee7333a0b0d9a9_man-office-helpdesk.webp"></div></figure><h3>Language</h3><p>Some companies outsource their IT across the globe, and although this may be financially tempting, there are risks involved.</p><p>Language barriers, cultural differences, international time zones, and a lack of understanding of local laws are just a few of the problems that could arise, along with data security and privacy issues depending upon the country&rsquo;s regulations.</p><p>Language barriers often lead to miscommunication and mistakes that can incur costs, so when considering an overseas firm, understand exactly how their service will be an asset to the company.&nbsp;</p><h3>Focused resources</h3><p>Technology develops at a tremendous pace, and it is imperative for IT support services to stay up to date. A company's internal IT department needs to invest significant time and money in technology to ensure all equipment and software are current. This, however, is carried out automatically by</p><p> <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/fully-managed-it-support">managed service providers</a>, who also give professional training to all staff members if required.</p><h3>Lower risk</h3><p>With 81% of company breaches attributed to weak passwords and a 30% surge in ransomware assaults, cybercrime is an issue that plagues the technology sector, and many businesses run a major risk of being victims. Therefore, any organisation must invest in reliable, secure software to avoid this.</p><p>IT companies are aware of these hazards and are skilled in managing and <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/top-tips-for-improving-your-business-cyber-security">preventing cybercrime</a>, such as phishing. A business that wants to reduce risk and avoid being one of the 800,000 consumers hacked yearly should invest in a reputable IT support firm.</p><h3>Reliability</h3><p>Every company that outsources IT support services are entitled to an exceptional degree of dependability and service; even though it may be challenging at the beginning to build trust, reliability is a significant factor.</p><p>The use of information technology in the workplace is crucial. Therefore, many companies choose to have an internal IT department. Unfortunately, this has drawbacks unless they have adequate, reliable staff to support this department.</p><p>Outsourced specialists who are on standby to handle company concerns and urgent needs, reduce stress and reassure all departments that their technology is well cared for by a dependable provider.</p><h3>Expertise</h3><p>Research is a critical component in the process of hiring an agency. A business will come across hundreds of well-known, highly qualified IT suppliers eager to take on new clients.</p><p>Check out credentials and reviews when conducting research, and request samples of work, before arranging face-to-face meetings, where clients will establish whether they feel a good relationship can be forged.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/63c6a4c3665e39386906f5d6_woman-teaching-computer.webp"></div></figure><h3>Tailored packages</h3><p>Tailored services are designed to meet individual customer needs and preferences, making them more personalised than generic services, which are often &lsquo;one-size-fits-all&rsquo; and less effective at meeting the specific needs of different customers.</p><p>Bespoke services operate more efficiently, as they are client-focused and therefore fit their needs perfectly, providing them with a convenient and efficient experience. This can help improve customer satisfaction and loyalty, leading to increased business sales and revenue.</p><h3>It is a business decision</h3><p>The benefit of outsourcing is that many capable IT companies are willing to accept a contract and reach a cost-effective agreement; this allows both parties to concentrate on their core skills.</p><h2>Why do certain companies outsource IT services?</h2><p>There are several justifications for corporate when outsourcing IT support. Smaller businesses typically find it more cost effective than employing someone directly, especially as IT services are only occasionally needed. Hence, they receive far more value for money instead of paying a wage.</p><p>Larger businesses often have internal IT departments but also outsource work concurrently for several reasons. The IT department is frequently overworked or requires special services such as cybersecurity, reporting, broadband management, disaster recovery, or monitoring.</p><h2>How can outsourcing IT support help a business?</h2><p>As software is constantly changing and updating, it can be difficult for a company to remain at the forefront of technology. When outsourcing, this problem is removed.</p><p>Managed service providers are experts in their field. They offer invaluable 24/7 monitoring, training, and assistance on new software, enabling individuals to navigate any day-to-day issues easily.</p><p>Choosing the <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/">best IT outsourcing company</a>is crucial for every organisation, so choose carefully. Once recruited, the proper IT support offers limitless benefits.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/63c680ad789555208b06ac15_Untitled%20(1024%20%C3%97%201024px)%20(2).png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[change-it-services-providers]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[10 Signs that it is Time to Change IT Services Providers]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[10-signs-that-it-is-time-to-change-it-providers]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60fa8]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 10 2023 15:33:05 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 08:47:51 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[10 Signs that it is Time to Change IT Providers]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Not satisfied with your current IT provider? Or frequently receiving sluggish service? Here are 10 signs that you should change your It provider Now!]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[51]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p><strong>Changing IT providers</strong>may appear to be more trouble than it&rsquo;s worth. Still, when considering lower costs, saved time, and improved service, an outsourced IT service is precisely what most successful businesses need.</p><p>Generally, companies continue to use the same <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/">IT provider</a>for prolonged periods due to convenience and dependability. However, it is essential to remember that every growing organisation deserves excellent IT management, and it is acceptable to seek out a different company that suits them.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/63c5702bc6651667653c1f8e_it-provider-stress.webp"></div></figure><h2>&zwj;<strong>What is an IT provider?</strong></h2><p>An IT provider is an independent company outsourced by businesses to ensure that their IT systems run smoothly, are updated regularly and remain secure while solving daily technical problems swiftly and efficiently. IT provider enables companies to focus on their core business operations without wasting time on frustrating IT issues.</p><p>Many offer fast broadband, giving smooth, seamless connections for multiple users, resolutions to cloud difficulties, strong cybersecurity, and disaster recovery. Another part of their service is report generation and training on new software while maintaining exceptional customer service and system performance.</p><h2><strong>Justifications for switching IT providers:</strong></h2><p>Switching your IT provider is an important decision that requires careful consideration of the changes' benefits and drawbacks. There are numerous reasons why switching IT providers may be a good idea, and weighing up all the pros and cons before making a final decision is essential.</p><p>Here are our top 10 reasons to justify making the switch, which should be taken into account when evaluating the available options:</p><h3>1. High costs and substandard results</h3><p>IT management is a crucial component in every organisation. Businesses today operate in a technology-driven environment; Therefore, delivering a reliable IT service is vital to smooth company operation. Just as competent <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/it-support">IT support</a>may increase capabilities, the same is true of ineffective assistance, which can seriously affect the company.</p><p>A recent survey found that 8% of small and medium UK businesses claim they have never received a contract from their MSP or admitted they have never read the terms and conditions. An agreement between a company and an outsourced IT provider will specify important information such as pricing ranges, technical specifications, and expected levels of customer service. Be warned, one example of a poor IT service is the absence of a contract.</p><h3><strong>2. Frequently receiving sluggish service</strong></h3><p>Reputable <a href="https://www.techtarget.com/searchitchannel/definition/managed-service-provider">managed service providers (MSP)</a>supply all clients with excellent transactional support, whether a large or small businesses. Additional extras such as impeccable customer service, transparent reports, and continued investment in their service should be included as standard and are the crucial differences between a low and high-quality provider.</p><p>An IT company is responsible for quickly and effectively resolving technology difficulties with committed customer care, often before the client realizes a problem. Sluggish service indicates an uncommitted company with poor standards and little desire to expand its customers' businesses.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/63c570bdf3c8d21a981f2471_office-it-support.webp"></div></figure><h3><strong>3. The IT provider is not equipped to handle emerging technology</strong></h3><p>Investing in new technology is vital to company success, and enthusiastic IT specialists understand that it can unlock business potential and give more freedom and security. They will urge companies to use these advancements as part of their regular contractual service. Although some organisations may be hesitant, new technology will not only significantly impact business growth but will also showcase the capability and confidence of the IT provider.</p><p>Those providers who do not embrace emerging technology and empower their clients with it are merely slowing them down and increasing the risk of cyber attacks from clever hackers.</p><h3>4. The unfamiliarity with other industries when Onboarding</h3><p>The onboarding process is vital to any contractual agreement when outsourcing to a new service provider. The IT business should have conducted in-depth research regarding their new client and created a robust understanding of their requirements and how they operate. This will enable the provision of specific or essential services, such as the need for 24/7 helpdesk support for hospitals.</p><h3><strong>5. Frequent below par IT system performance</strong></h3><p>Fast and efficient IT performance is an essential part of everyday life, therefore ensuring technology systems are running to optimum efficiency is a fundamental requirement of a service provider.</p><p>Frequent substandard performance can negatively impact an organisation and frustrate the end user. The outsourced IT company should ensure this never happens and endeavour to resolve any problems that arise quickly and efficiently, as system flaws lead to dissatisfied clients, a drop in business, and a stressful work environment.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/63c570c912b0af2f2f345899_it-system-support.webp"></div></figure><h3><strong>6. Irregular and weak communication with the IT provider</strong></h3><p>A company needs effective communication throughout the workplace to succeed, meet deadlines, and surpass goals. This should be no different when considering outsourced IT providers, as relationships are essential to expanding businesses.</p><p>Experiencing difficult communication is unacceptable and should signal that it may be time to re-evaluate the expectations and requirements of an existing IT team.</p><h3><strong>7. An Account Manager has not been provided</strong></h3><p>Account management aims to establish a comprehensive connection between larger companies and the IT support service, improving relationships and adding value to the service provided.</p><p>The effective utilisation of an Account Manager enables the development of a reliable, enduring connection and the delivery of a top-notch IT service, promoting customer satisfaction and, most importantly, loyalty.</p><p>Those support providers that do not offer an Account Manager risk a lack of cohesion between the client and an absence of understanding regarding the company's goals and aspirations, as there is no personal connection.</p><h3><strong>8. The IT provider fails to evolve with company demands</strong></h3><p>Expansion and growth are critical aspects of any business. As a company naturally expands, there will be frequent changes in the workplace, such as technological advances, growth in staffing, and larger profit margins.</p><p>An exceptional IT provider will anticipate these changes, take the opportunity to accommodate the expansion, make suggestions for further growth and ensure the company can update software, develop its support structure, and review its cyber security accordingly.</p><p>IT companies that do not keep up with the needs of clients can cause damage to reputation and repress growth.</p><h3><strong>9. The IT provider often generates reports late and incomplete</strong></h3><p>Monitoring reports that are comprehensive and issued when expected are a fundamental part of an MSP service that can critically impact the business by overseeing employee productivity, reducing infrastructure costs, and enhancing data flow.</p><p>Regular inspections are imperative to understand how every business performs from the inside, and providers will encourage clients to review, digest, and act on the information presented.</p><p>Experiencing late or incomplete reports could indicate that the IT provider is not monitoring the servers correctly or keeping track of business requirements, which can seriously affect productivity and operation.</p><h3>10. A business will frequently handle IT issues rather than contact its IT provider</h3><p>IT issues are usual in all businesses, as technology can't function correctly 100% of the time. An outsourced MSP will train employees in self-help methods to encourage them to fix simple problems themselves.</p><p>Unfortunately, some outsourced companies can have significant waiting times and unhelpful customer services that employees will quickly lose faith in. An IT firm is contractually obligated to help resolve any IT issues and should fix technical problems either before they arise or immediately after they have occurred.</p><p>If an IT supplier is not performing in a way that is expected or that was specified in a contract, a meeting with both parties should be held to address this issue. If the conclusion is not satisfactory, it is time to change provider.</p><p>Read more: <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/10-factors-to-consider-when-outsourcing-it-support-services"><strong>10 Factors to Consider when Outsourcing IT Support Services</strong></a></p><h2><strong>Summary</strong></h2><p>Working with a provider who fits your business model in every way is essential. If any of the above points have flagged a warning or hit a nerve? then it is time to make the change and see how a new <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/fully-managed-it-support">Managed Service Provider</a>can help drive your business forward!</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/63bd876420da86691f18255d_Untitled%20(1024%20%C3%97%201024px).png]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/63bd876420da86691f18255d_Untitled%20(1024%20%C3%97%201024px).png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[why-you-should-outsource-it-services]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[5 Main Reasons Why Your Company Should Outsource It's IT Services]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[5-main-reasons-why-your-company-should-outsource-its-it-services]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e1e]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:07 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 08:23:21 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Outsource IT Services - 5 Main Reasons | TechVertu]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[This blog discusses the benefits of outsourced IT services and mentions why it is crucial for your company.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[32]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>Here at TechVertu, we provide outsourced <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/it-support">IT support</a>for all manner of businesses. Included in this list are five of the main reasons why we believe having a dedicated team of IT technicians working alongside your business is so important.</p><h2>Diverse pool of experience</h2><p>Having a wealth of knowledge from all different IT backgrounds means we can cover a wide range of IT topics. From Networking to Printer Management, from Office 365 to Antivirus, someone will always be ready to assist.</p><h2>Business growth</h2><p>Introducing new technologies to keep up with the needs of the business&nbsp;is&nbsp;referred&nbsp;to as Scalability.&nbsp;We can test and implement IT solutions alongside business development to ensure that nothing is slowing you down and you are always up to date.</p><p>Read More: <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/10-factors-to-consider-when-outsourcing-it-support-services">Factors to Consider when Outsourcing IT Support Services</a></p><h2>Refined security</h2><p>We put&nbsp;enhanced security features across all of&nbsp;your&nbsp;company&rsquo;s network and keep it secure.&nbsp;If&nbsp;a machine became compromised it would become locked down;&nbsp;if a device were to be stolen, we could track its location. We know how important your data is and we go all out in protecting it.</p><h2>Consistent preventative support</h2><p>Nobody likes to be left behind when it comes to technology. We test&nbsp;current builds&nbsp;to find any issues and apply fixes before they become a problem. We also monitor every device to ensure everything stays up to date and clear of any issues.</p><h2>Controlled IT costs</h2><p>Paying&nbsp;for IT repairs, as and when you need them,&nbsp;is a costly affair. We offer fixed price support solutions which can match the needs of your business, ensuring you are covered for any issues. From laptop setup to disaster recovery, we will support&nbsp;all your business&rsquo; IT needs.&nbsp;</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a30689cb06f28421ef7e3c_tech-outsource.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a30689cb06f28421ef7e3c_tech-outsource.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[cartoon-contest-gallery]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[Cartoon Contest - 2021]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[cartoon-contest]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e40]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:10 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Thu Oct 12 2023 13:52:16 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Cartoon Contest 2021 - TechVertu]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[TechVertu organised this ground-breaking International Cartoon Contest to pass our corporate message to the public.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[53]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>As an <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/it-support">innovative IT Support</a>and Technology company, TechVertu knows very well the importance of increasing public awareness concerning Information Technology Challenges in today&rsquo;s personal and business environment. Thus, we organised this ground-breaking International Cartoon Contest to pass our corporate message to the public.</p><p>The following online gallery includes all the artwork submitted to TechVertu for our first International Cartoon Contest. The title of this Cartoon Competition is &ldquo;<strong>IT &amp; Technology challenges for businesses.&rdquo;</strong></p><h3>Jury members for TechVertu First International Cartoon Contest - 2021</h3><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b33a60eed20098a59c83_The-Jury-1024x405.png"></div></figure><h3><strong>Don&rsquo;t miss the extraordinary artwork featured on the following pages.</strong></h3><p>All displayed artworks are sent to TechVertu by individual artists under the Terms and Conditions stated in the Contest Invitation Letter provided to them before their submission. Although TechVertu has undertaken precautious assessments on these artworks to ensure they are in line with the competition's Terms and Conditions, the company is not responsible for the artwork's originality and copyright aspect. The legal terms were explained to the candidate clearly; therefore, such an issue should be the artist's responsibility who submitted the work for this contest.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1cf25dc688354b4b5c508_TechVertu-Cartoon-Contest-2021.png]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1cf25dc688354b4b5c508_TechVertu-Cartoon-Contest-2021.png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff8471885ba144fa670e5a_Agim%20Krasniqi%20-%20KrAgi%20-%2001.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff8471036577a335ebff03_Agim%20Krasniqi%20-%20KrAgi%20-%2002.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff84715552a664e897cae4_Agim%20Krasniqi%20-%20KrAgi%20-%2003.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff84710229051a00ec3395_Agim%20Krasniqi%20-%20KrAgi%20-%2004.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff8471bf4f01729128fb42_Agim%20Krasniqi.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff847faa1e872403626979_Shmidt%20Alexander%20-%20Russia%20-%2001.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff847fd85827f83c3e86b8_Shmidt%20Alexander%20-%20Russia%20-%2002.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff847fbd0873b4c43b04b7_Shmidt%20Alexander%20-%20Russia%20-%2003.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff847fae71a56cb1b8a009_Shmidt%20Alexander%20-%20Russia%20-%2004.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff847f88c1c7f0a4ebacbd_Shmidt%20Alexander%20-%20Russia%20-%2005.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff848fbd087380c23b04ff_TechVertu1A4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff848f7b1b534eabe337b6_TechVertu2A4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff848f86a574495a01aba4_TechVertu3A4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff848fc7c585171a52b1e6_TechVertu4A4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff849a28fc3cbf3c3bd1aa_AplicacionesHumanas.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff849a88c1c7ae6eebae20_AutoEmpleoOnLine.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff849a3e23d96399aee6e2_EducacionDigital.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff849a972a54d702a7b971_LaCondena.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff849af42b34341f416ccd_REINICIAR.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff84a3f6bfe9490cdac661_Immobilizing%20expert.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff84a3198334449ab55c8b_in%20the%20sights.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff84a328fc3c43363bd1f0_mask%20of%20violence.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff84a3972a546915a7bc9f_matiusk.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62ff84a35552a69ce397ccf5_taming%20the%20horse.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0021a3b284885e042672_it1%20cai%20weidong%20china.jpg]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e00284dcb0957221246d2_it2cai%20weidong%20china.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e00285fffcc56bb307f68_it3%20cai%20weidong%20china.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e00280edca0b3d94d26dd_it4%20cai%20weidong%20china.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e00281c19f0ceda84699a_it5cai%20weidong%20china.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e002876e7267f9bb2ae81_it6cai%20weidong%20china.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e037a39ea85c93df2b00f_1TV%20Cartoon.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e037a4a4625172d218d57_1TV%20Cartoon-02.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e037a72bbf012e6f50054_1TV%20Cartoon-03.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0384a98b279fc746bf4e_CONSTANTIN%20PAVEL%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0384e7f2ddefb4429023_CONSTANTIN%20PAVEL%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e03846671aa54527251ea_CONSTANTIN%20PAVEL%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0390082485cec4921b67_Amor%20i%20tablet.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0390082485c088921b66_Cuka.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0390de535e57e9dc5ad4_email%20pokloni.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e039022283fcdfecd2251_ON%20LINE%20%20POP.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e03910c10d288a408c3d0_prst%20i%20nos.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0390a3b2846246044bb7_Recycle%20bin.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e03901739663f75fcc446_robot%20and%20corona.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0390bf383e1198b0a691_trap.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e039ec56e3484d262ede5_GEORGOPALIS_001.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e039e134c38da98ae46da_GEORGOPALIS_002.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e039e7d3a676ec5192bbd_GEORGOPALIS_003.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e039e22283f4cc0cd2273_GEORGOPALIS_004.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e046904d2d63157724b9f_Li%20Bu%20Yi%20%E2%80%93%20China-1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04728d845a34113dfa69_Li%20Bu%20Yi%20%E2%80%93%20China-4.jpg]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e03d362d630a20a2ae0fb_Doru%20Axinte-Romania%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e03d3a3b284b15c044e86_Doru%20Axinte-Romania%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e03d3747fe74e16316abd_Doru%20Axinte-Romania%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e03e05fffcc7370309f9f_esmaeil%20babaei-iran-1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e03e07d3a674d03192c9e_esmaeil%20babaei-iran-2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e03e00edca03e5f4d5b01_esmaeil%20babaei-iran-3.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e03e004d2d6fb967245fc_esmaeil%20babaei-iran-4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e03e0291883c0c3e102be_esmaeil%20babaei-iran-5.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e03ef1c19f0f4fd8485c8_Fadi%20Abou%20Hassan.%20Norway%2002.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e03eff1be88b3c36e061e_Fadi%20Abou%20Hassan.Norway%2001.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e03fb72bbf021b8f50238_Huseyin%20Cakmak%20(Cyprus)%20Technology%20Challenges.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e040708248513c0921ee3_ILYA_KATZ_1_.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0407cc9f7a5293028f03_ILYA_KATZ_2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04070c10d2232108c850_ILYA_KATZ_3_.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0407de535e37ccdc5cac_ILYA_KATZ_4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04070db05b287e53c636_ILYA_KATZ_5.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04172e5489580df1635f_Num%C3%A9risation_20210308.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04177d3a67fa7a192dd3_Num%C3%A9risation_20210623%20(2).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0417be7519292a8771bb_Num%C3%A9risation_20210623%20(3).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e041776e7263883b2d324_Num%C3%A9risation_20210623%20(4).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0417747fe7bb56316d34_Num%C3%A9risation_20210623%20(5).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e041730b1d305b61dc5a1_Num%C3%A9risation_20210623.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0b7d4a4625507921eb7a_Makhmudjon%20Eshonkulov_Uzbekistan_03.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0b840824852f889288cc_Makhmudjon%20Eshonkulov_Uzbekistan_02.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0b897d3a6777c3196907_Makhmudjon%20Eshonkulov_Uzbekistan_01.jpg]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e042fb93ffd4ba890ddcb_642-in..jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e042f17396675b8fccbd7_Karikatura%20-%20133.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e042fde535e7215dc5d6e_mobi-a3.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e042f0c10d268c908c9f9_usb.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04890db05b05c953c97a_Grigori%20Katz-1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0489cc9f7a755b0293ec_Grigori%20Katz-2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04896671aa599b726699_Grigori%20Katz-3.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04890c10d201fa08ce49_Grigori%20Katz-4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04894a4625b017219b53_Grigori%20Katz-5.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04951739669c33fcd117_Cartoon%20(1).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0495b284c63f44abb609_Cartoon%20(3).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04950db05b5dbe53c9ee_Cartoon%20(4).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e049504d2d6d6e5724cac_Cartoon%20(5).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04954dcb09686a127f06_Cartoon%20(6).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04a57e234a2a0850a4d8_Kazanchev_Ukraine_01.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04a5e7f2ddc974429b65_Kazanchev_Ukraine_02.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04a5219e96116d921daa_Kazanchev_Ukraine_03.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04a5291883019de108b8_Kazanchev_Ukraine_04.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04a562d63019a32aea82_Kazanchev_Ukraine_05.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04b75fffcc5c1030a549_Li%20Hai%20Feng%20%E2%80%93%20China%20-%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04b7be7519a1df8781ba_Li%20Hai%20Feng%20%E2%80%93%20China%20-%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04b7219e966a8f921eac_Li%20Hai%20Feng%20%E2%80%93%20China%20-%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04d1173966dfacfcd48f_liu-qiang-china-1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04d78d845a5c7c3dfccb_liu-qiang-china-2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e04decb00f1e8ef0ca231_liu-qiang-china-3.jpg]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0b9e219e9667749249ce_liu-qiang-china-4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bac92151dd113c29272_1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bac0c10d26a52091f7f_2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bac082485fa26928a06_3.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bac8d845ae5c43e40a9_4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bc3291883951be16a56_Makmun%20Kariming%20%E2%80%93%20Indonesia-New%20generation%20and%20addicted%20to%20new%20generation.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bc3cd22fa1178e1bc2d_Makmun%20Kariming%20%E2%80%93%20Indonesia-On-Line%20Education.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bc3cd22faac37e1bc2c_Makmun%20Kariming%20%E2%80%93%20Indonesia-Sale%20for%20millenial.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bcf0edca003104dcc71_02.07.2021.Mihatov1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bcfb93ffd76c19135ea_02.07.2021.Mihatov2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bcf04d2d61e01728962_02.07.2021.Mihatov3.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bcf68a00e2bf0792c29_02.07.2021.Mihatov4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bdd5ff737c4a201c6fb_Hacker.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bdd134c38c418aea1ec_Postman.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bf430b1d3a5511e0184_teknoloj-yar%C4%B1%C5%9Fma.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bf32918835c07e16abc_teknoloj-yar%C4%B1%C5%9Fma-2%20copy.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bf42918837f5ce16abd_teknoloj-yar%C4%B1%C5%9Fma-3%20copy.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bf45fffccd355310040_teknoloj-yar%C4%B1%C5%9Fma-4%20copy.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0bf4a7ad3f5009c63246_teknoloj-yar%C4%B1%C5%9Fma-5%20copy.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c064e0ef56550368ddb_ali%20shafei-iran-TechVertu%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c061c19f021cb84d410_ali%20shafei-iran-TechVertu%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c060c22d9335e44cbf5_ali%20shafei-iran-TechVertu%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c125ff7372f4501c7f1_Alireza%20Pakdel-Iran-(1).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c125fffcc3c563100ec_Alireza%20Pakdel-Iran-(2).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c26c9c0542a14044752_1.jpg]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c2e4dcb0910f212d924_2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c2e0edca0381d4dd40c_3.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c2e0c10d274eb092317_4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c2e08248556a0928bff_5.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c3be23263396f5df0d7_I.T%20Cartoon%201%20copy.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c4c6671aa33a072bd7c_Bulent%20OKTAY%20-%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c4cbf383e768db10e67_Bulent%20OKTAY%20-%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c4c0c22d92f0544ce39_Bulent%20OKTAY%20-%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c56a98b2723bc470b6c_car%202098.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c567e234a0fd35107c5_danger.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c621c19f0595384d72a_Davoud%20Deldar%20-%20Iran.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c6d1c19f0216784d76a_Dejan%20Borkovi%C4%87%20-%20Serbia%20-%20Factory.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c764e0ef519d3368fc9_Eray%20Ozbek-Turkey%20-%20cartoon.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c941739663195fd64a9__Intrusive%20ads__%20Izabela%20Kowalska-Wieczorek-%20Poland.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c940824852d9c928f85__Online%20payment__%20Izabela%20Kowalska-Wieczorek_%20Poland.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0c9f6671aad81d72c100_jiaru%20ijun%20-%20China.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0cac6671aa19c872c123_J15.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0cac2e5489fd58f1c25f_jh.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0cace232633a525df2ec_jin2-A4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0cacde535e368fdcad00_jj91.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0cac134c3887aeaea4ee_JXXA4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ccd0c10d23577092715_Klaus%20Pitter%20-%20Austria%20-%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0cd34dcb09976412e1b3_Klaus%20Pitter%20-%20Austria%20-%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0cd97d3a67313e1977ca_Klaus%20Pitter%20-%20Austria%20-%203.jpg]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0cde5ff7372f4b01cdf6_Klaus%20Pitter%20-%20Austria%20-%204.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ce476e726a6a3b32948_Klaus%20Pitter%20-%20Austria%20-%205.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0cef0edca0643f4ddc32_LUIS%20EDUARDO%20LEON%20%E2%80%93%20Colombia%20-%20INGLATERRA%2002%20-%20%202021.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0cef5ff7373b3c01cf39_LUIS%20EDUARDO%20LEON%20%E2%80%93%20Colombia%20-%20INGLATERRA%2003%20-%20%202021.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0cef747fe7f6af31c711_LUIS%20EDUARDO%20LEON%20%E2%80%93%20Colombia%20-%20INGLATERRA%2004%20-%20%202021.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0cef0c10d226ac092797_LUIS%20EDUARDO%20LEON%20%E2%80%93%20Colombia%20-INGLATERRA%2001%20-%20%202021.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0cfc5ff737610901cf6d_Mahdieh%20Sabbaghkar%20-%20dream.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0cfc1739665bc3fd6f54_Mahdieh%20Sabbaghkar%20-%20Iranconfuse.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0cfc4dcb092b9d12e3f5_Mahdieh%20Sabbaghkar%20-%20robot1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d08747fe75ea231c77d_Mihai%20Ignat%20-%20Romania%20-%20IGNAT1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d080c22d992ee44dc95_Mihai%20Ignat%20-%20Romania%20-%20IGNAT2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d08e7f2ddf2a0430d38_Mihai%20Ignat%20-%20Romania%20-%20IGNAT4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d085ff737a1d501cfa0_Mihai%20Ignat%20-%20Romania%20-%20IGNAT7.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d087e234a4307511747_Mihai%20Ignat%20-%20Romania%20-%20IGNAT9.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d1368a00e2d75793b6f_omer2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d132918833515e17278_omercam1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d204e0ef5400e36977a_obaid-sudan.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d3668a00e2588793f3e_Rupert%20Kemble%20-%20UK%20-%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d36c18b813c71f942bc_Rupert%20Kemble%20-%20UK%20-%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d41a3b284a30604c095_saeed%20moosarezaei-%20iran-%20scarecrow.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d4f37a9cb265451ec49_backup_%20Salar%20Eshratkhah%20_%20Iran.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d4f4a4625db7421fd23_Confession%20to%20a%20priest_%20Salar%20Eshratkhah%20_%20%20Iran.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d4f76e7261b14b32c9e_Contract%20_%20Salar%20Eshratkhah%20_%20Iran.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d4f4e0ef5dca6369ab9_drone%20dog_%20Salar%20Eshratkhah%20_%20%20Iran.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d4fb284c690bdac430c_Evolution%20_%20Salar%20Eshratkhah%20_%20%20Iran.jpg]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d66a3b2840c5b04c130_Tenev%20Zhivko%20%E2%80%93%20GISSEN%20-%20Bulgaria%20-%20Cartoon%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d66e7f2dd8f3543109f_Tenev%20Zhivko%20%E2%80%93%20GISSEN%20-%20Bulgaria%20-%20Cartoon%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d7172bbf000d0f56b47_Yalda%20Hasheminezhad%20-1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d71134c384eeeaea9a5_Yalda%20Hasheminezhad%20-2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d719f0a7e9813f851ce_Yalda%20Hasheminezhad%20-3.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d85cc9f7a06cb03016c_In%20tab%20we%20trust.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d8568a00e18ce79417c_tab%20commandment.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d917e186085bca221bc_agus%20widodo_image%20of%20justice05.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d910c22d9010344e73e_AGUSWIDODO_08.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d912918837a33e174fc_economycartoon01.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d915fffcc746e311ae4_teknologi02.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d91a98b275290471589_To%20Bring.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d9b4e0ef59920369c34_1%20-%20Ahmad%20Reza%20Sohrabi%20-%20Iran.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d9b92151ddeacc2aa75_2%20-%20Ahmad%20Reza%20Sohrabi%20-%20Iran.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0d9bbf383ecf8bb1257e_3%20-%20Ahmad%20Reza%20Sohrabi%20-%20Iran.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0daac9c0549cbd0458a1_Akbar%20Rouhy-iran%20-01.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0daa37a9cb25c951edd0_akbar%20rouhy-iran%20-02.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0daabe75191d1887dec2_akbar%20rouhy-iran%20-03.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0db6b284c64f41ac4aff_Agrifuture.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0db6a7ad3fe3b2c63d69_Artificial%20Intelligence.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0db6cc9f7a22980301fd_received_694573367806607~2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0dce747fe7507131cc39_1st%20Concurso%20de%20dibujos%20animados%20de%20TV1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0dd6c02f0511432fc32f_1st%20Concurso%20de%20dibujos%20animados%20de%20TV2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ddfcc9f7a50dc0302b0_1st%20Concurso%20de%20dibujos%20animados%20de%20TV3.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0de5e23263a0035e064f_1st%20Concurso%20de%20dibujos%20animados%20de%20TV4.jpg]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0dec0824852d28929542_1st%20Concurso%20de%20dibujos%20animados%20de%20TV5.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0dfa747fe7e45631ccf4_Pais_e_filhos.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e0568a00e7b5c7944c3_1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e0505150493cd42200e_2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e054a46257b3822005d_3.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e05c56e341b92634e4c_4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e107e186015cfa22952_1St%20TV%20Cartoon_AnonAnindito.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e1a76e726188bb332e9_SKMBT_C45221041123560.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e2404d2d6e559729b59_Bahram%20Arjmandnia-1st%20TV%20Cartoons%20Contest-1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e24cb00f19a150d0557_Bahram%20Arjmandnia-1st%20TV%20Cartoons%20Contest-2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e2492151d13e6c2afb9_Bahram%20Arjmandnia-1st%20TV%20Cartoons%20Contest-3.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e2437a9cb387a51f00d_Bahram%20Arjmandnia-1st%20TV%20Cartoons%20Contest-4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e30c9c0540567045d78_0fd10e7c-aa3e-4b6f-8bbd-ffc7b70fc89d.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e30082485a49b929610_3910aaa1-7be4-4e00-b457-b8abfa24ea4a.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e3037a9cb719251f031_abdce6bd-e986-4ec8-b141-4a2263fc9856.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e30be7519ce9787e181_d69219fa-7cc7-410c-9ae8-092a3baadddd.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e3bdd57f22967d717b9_Afsan-1442.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e3b219e9648e99261f3_Afsan-1615.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e47a7ad3f0296c64189_dog_tail.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e47a3b284603c04c413_Leaf%20Fall.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e4704d2d60b21729ddd_robotique.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e5292151d1378c2b31f_20210708_165313%20(1).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e522918832295e17bd0_general.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e5ee2326380fb5e0dcb_derkaoui%20cartoon.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0efd219e968458926f84_FatemehEkrami.jpg]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e777d3a672078198a07__Social%20Media.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e7768a00e26ff7947d0_Remote%20meetings.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e77747fe7e39331ceb5_Social%20media%20effect..jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e77219e966bc192667e_Work%20from%20home1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e770db05b1d9554267f_Work%20from%20home2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e91219e9681949268de_Don%20Quixote%20-%20Dragan%20Stojanovic%20-%20Serbia.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e91e2326328225e0e77_Identity%20-%20Dragan%20Stojanovic%20-%20Serbia.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0e91e7f2ddbb3b431733_Wi-Fi%20-%20Dragan%20Stojanovic%20-%20Serbia.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ea0458984581d005620_efat%20amjadipoor%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ea09f0a7e060af863fb_efat%20amjadipoor%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ea01739663021fd7dda_efat%20amjadipoor%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ea092151d29f4c2b67c_efat%20amjadipoor%204.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ead30b1d301f91e1c6f_Ehsan%20Cheraghi%20IRANSHAHI%20-%20IRAN%20-%20(1).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ead0515048c6d42271d_Ehsan%20Cheraghi%20IRANSHAHI%20-%20IRAN%20-%20(2).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ead9f0a7eaba1f86449_Ehsan%20Cheraghi%20IRANSHAHI%20-%20IRAN%20-%20(3).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ead76e72636a9b33a41_Ehsan%20Cheraghi%20IRANSHAHI%20-%20IRAN%20-%20(4).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ead22283f4069cda608_Ehsan%20Cheraghi%20IRANSHAHI%20-%20IRAN%20-%20(5).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ebacd22fafd8ce1d61d_EG-CT-Scann-Insta%20(1).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ebacb00f1832f0d088b_Tech-EhsanGanji-IRAN%20(1).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0eba5ff737394c01d5d9_Tech-EhsanGanji-IRAN%20(2).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0eba0db05b6984542722_Tech-EhsanGanji-IRAN%20(3).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ebadd57f2dc34d71de6_Tech-EhsanGanji-IRAN%20(4).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ed0c9c054e12804624b_Elham%20Khalili%20Mehr%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ed0134c3859ffaeb0c6_Elham%20Khalili%20Mehr%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ed01c19f0ded584fe56_Elham%20Khalili%20Mehr%203.jpg]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ed6cc9f7aa6810309e6_Elham%20Khalili%20Mehr%204.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ed61c19f0dd2584fe8c_Elham%20Khalili%20Mehr%205.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ee35ff737473c01d654_Fan%20Lintao%20cartoon%20work(China)1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ee3de535e6534dcc142_Fan%20Lintao%20cartoon%20work(China)2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ee3a98b273dd8473083_Fan%20Lintao%20cartoon%20work(China)3.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f0ebe7519573887e549_img505.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f0ef1be8833e06e80ec_img545.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f0e7e1860fa91a237e7_img546.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f19de535e6394dcc232_Frederick%20AA%20_%2001.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f286671aa3bf472d6cd_Frederick%20AA%20_%2002.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f340db05b6cb4542a91_Goran%20Divac%20%2C%20Srbija%20%2C%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f3430b1d3b5f81e1e18_Goran%20Divac%20%2C%20Srbija%20%2C%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f4068a00e5c3c794d0f_Heibat%20Ahmadi%20-%20Iran%20(1).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f406671aaf41772d70c_Heibat%20Ahmadi%20-%20Iran%20(2).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f40cc9f7a296f030b6a_Heibat%20Ahmadi%20-%20Iran%20(3).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f401c19f0433d8502fa_Heibat%20Ahmadi%20-%20Iran%20(4).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f4e39ea8548def34393_Hamid%20Ghalijari-Iran-01.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f4d7d3a670b5519996c_Hamid%20Ghalijari-Iran-02.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f4dbf383e21e5b12fd1_Hamid%20Ghalijari-Iran-03.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f4d2918830491e18426_Hamid%20Ghalijari-Iran-04.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f4e04d2d642bf72a486_Hamid%20Ghalijari-Iran-05.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f67bf383e797ab13074_Hasan%20Ismail%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f672e54895d7af1d32a_Hasan%20Ismail%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f67a98b27c458473757_Hasan%20Ismail%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f670c10d23dcf093920_Hasan%20Ismail%204.jpg]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f6da98b275f1e47377e_Hasan%20Ismail%205.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f7a0c10d2b03709395c_HI%CC%87LAL%20O%CC%88ZCAN-TURKEY-EDUCATI%CC%87ON%20FROM%20HOME%20.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f7ac1752424bd710ae5_HI%CC%87LAL%20O%CC%88ZCAN-TURKEY-EDUCATI%CC%87ON%20FROM%20HOME.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f7aa98b27458a473828_HI%CC%87LAL%20O%CC%88ZCAN-TURKEY-MERCURY%20RETROGRADE%20.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f7a68a00e43aa794f39_HI%CC%87LAL%20O%CC%88ZCAN-TURKEY-MODERN%20HUNT.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f876327607cb3a2b6a5_Petry%20and%20Crisan%20-%20Romania%20-%20Cancer.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f8739ea856a11f34552_Petry%20and%20Crisan%20-%20Romania%20-%20Modern%20Sisyphus.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f8798af82106621b8f4_Petry%20and%20Crisan%20-%20Romania%20-%20The%20Beginning%20Kit.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0f955ff7377f0701e2ab_jamal%20rahmati%20iraniannnn.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0fa372bbf06b63f58044_Javad%20Abdolhoseini%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0fa3c56e34d5ea635ed7_Javad%20Abdolhoseini%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0fb0c18b819652f95bc4_Criminals%20-Socaial%20Media%20and%20Press.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0fb0a98b27930c473981_tech%20-%20peace.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0fb0b93ffdfdc6916443_technology%20-%20prodoctivity.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0fbd4a4625a2602218ab_Mahna%20Yazdani-cartoon01.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0fbd76e726797db3414d_mahnaz-yazdani-cartoon02.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0fbd7e234a75e3514214_mahnaz-yazdani-cartoon03.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0fbd1c19f04cfa850d97_mahnaz-yazdani-cartoon04.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0fe09f2fad19f6f6905b_Mahshid%20Hashemi%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0fe0b284c66157ac57e2_Mahshid%20Hashemi%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0fe00c10d24f29093afa_Mahshid%20Hashemi%204.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0fe0bf383ed5e7b135ec_Mahshid%20Hashemi%205.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ff068a00e1e5a7951ee_1-Majid%20Salehi.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e0ff07e234a6cb251495a_2-Majid%20Salehi%20.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10066671aa7ea672de62_Malatesh%20Garadimani_INDIA%20_1.jpg]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e100e62d63074352b6d80_Malatesh%20Garadimani_INDIA%20_2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e100e5ff737fda101e5ec_Malatesh%20Garadimani_INDIA%20_3.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e100ea3b2844d2d04d122_Malatesh%20Garadimani_INDIA%20_4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e100ec56e34264c6361ff_Malatesh%20Garadimani_INDIA%20_5.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e101bdd57f27386d73c8d_mansoure%20dehghani.%20Online%20violence.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e101b2e54891b8cf1d9b7_mansoure%20dehghani.Cybersecurity%20Threats.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e101b68a00e1af2795432_mansoure.dehghani.Work%20from%20home.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10290824854edb92a2c3_android%20gaga.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1036be7519c27587ee44_mobile.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1042632760ebe9a2c49f_modem.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10554e0ef5ccdf36c3c6_Voloshyn%20Work%20from%20home.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10617e234ae579514e72_Nahid%20Maghsoudi%2C.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e106f051504237c423baf_Neda%20Tanhaee%20Moghadda-1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10700515040e44423bb0_Neda%20Tanhaee%20Moghadda-2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1070cb00f1e1cb0d27b3_Neda%20Tanhaee%20Moghadda-3.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1070219e962b0e927e5f_Neda%20Tanhaee%20Moghadda-4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1070632760a9c9a2c81f_Neda%20Tanhaeimoghadam%206.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e107f4dcb09f04013108f_unconnected.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1096219e9677f3927ee7_Pooya%20Abdoli%20(1).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1096051504329e423c4c_Pooya%20Abdoli%20(2).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1096a3b2842ee904d7e3_Pooya%20Abdoli%20(3).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e109637a9cb8dac520845_Pooya%20Abdoli%20(4).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1096dd57f2697ad74059_Pooya%20Abdoli%20(5).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10964dcb091f3a1312d0_Pooya%20Abdoli%20(6).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10a8051504783a423cb7_Prawit%20Mongkolnowrut.jpg]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10b5c1752438c3711835_cartoon%20tema%20TI.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10c9082485102792a60f_IT-1-Resad-Sultanovic-Bosnia-Herzegovina.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10c968a00e94fb79587e_IT-2-Resad-Sultanovic-Bosnia-Herzegovina.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10c9a3b28447ae04d967_IT-3-Resad-Sultanovic-Bosnia-Herzegovina.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10c9f1be88c08b6e8ae7_IT-4-Resad-Sultanovic-Bosnia-Herzegovina.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10c97e234a72b25157db_IT-5-Resad-Sultanovic-Bosnia-Herzegovina.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10d52de75c0ff8969e98_AI%20EVOLUTION%20%20(2).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10d5bf383e9001b13a54_CONTROLANDO%20A%20LOS%20MEDIOS%2002.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10d5e7f2dd0d304331d0_EL%20MEJOR%20AMIGO%2002.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10d56671aa593572e5d4_HUMANIDAD%20Y%20TECNOLOGIA%2002.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10d568a00e5af47958f9_LA%20TRAMPA%2002.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10e31c19f0b92885167e_attack.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10e3c02f05f19b2fddf9_wifi%20free.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10e3de535e8107dccaee_wifi.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e10f329188350e4e1977f_Sami%20sawari.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e110462d630dc442b7740_Shahrokh%20Heidari%20-%20child%20gambeling.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11047d3a67236919ac34_Shahrokh%20Heidari%20-%20loading.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1104134c3806acaec15f_Shahrokh%20Heidari%20-%20social-medias.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e110439ea85798cf356df_Shahrokh%20Heidari%20Contaminated-shahrokh%20heidari%20france.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11044e0ef5fcf336cc32_shahrokh-heidari-france-Safety-at-work-04.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e111398af8219b721ce30_Shen%20Hong%20Li%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1113b284c63202ac70d0_Shen%20Hong%20Li%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1113e7f2dd158b43360a_Shen%20Hong%20Li%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1113c02f0564b12fded9_Shen%20Hong%20Li%204.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1113173966fb4ffd98f9_Shen%20Hong%20Li%205.jpg]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e113005150487c44241b4_Junk%20information-PengShisong.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11306327609671a2cf6a_The%20keyboard%20hero-PengShisong.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e113cc56e348061637270_Siminoga%20Vadim%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e113cbe75190e5787f84b_Siminoga%20Vadim%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e113c0c10d21683094651_Siminoga%20Vadim%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e113c62d63040702b80d3_Siminoga%20Vadim%204.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e113c92151d2f0bc2d054_Siminoga%20Vadim%205.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1148082485a96092a84a_Soham%20Roy.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11555edb522a324ab987_Sohrab%20Kheiri%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1155cd22fa135ce1eae4_Sohrab%20Kheiri%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1155219e96bafc9288e0_Sohrab%20Kheiri%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e116a1739663cd2fd9a6b_Somitazahra%20-%20Setarehaseman.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1177c18b815905f96838_sunshenying-china-01.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11770db05bd6745440c4_sunshenying-china-03.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11772e54898370f1e55f_sunshenying-china-3.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e118a37a9cb27db5210f1_Tayebe%20Khalili%20Mehr%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e118abe75199f8787fcea_Tayebe%20Khalili%20Mehr%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e118abe7519819687fce9_Tayebe%20Khalili%20Mehr%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e118a7e1860a41ba25302_Tayebe%20Khalili%20Mehr%204.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e118a98af826bda21d68b_Tayebe%20Khalili%20Mehr%205.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11975ff737f9f201ef93_Venugopal%20Galisetty%20-%20IT%20CHALLENGES-1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11ad4dcb0940301319bf_Black%20Sun_Bondar.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11ad4e0ef5800d36d0f3_Gear_Bondar.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11ad04d2d65aad72c8c0_Mushroomer_Bondar.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11ad76e7261943b35b07_Stop%20Online%20Violence_Bondar.jpg]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11ba082485ecb992b53e_Cloudy%20treat_Bondar.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11c6173966818cfd9c67_Krumpolec_Slovakia_2020-1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11d22de75c0aae96ae93_Weng%20Lifeng%E2%80%94China-Everyone%20is%20a%20CEO.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11de0edca07c524e1039_wissam%20cartoon.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11f3b284c62194ac826c_Abbas%20Naaseri-Iran-01.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11ffcb00f17f840d3ac7_Bernard%20Bouton%20phone%20booth.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e11ffcb00f12f130d3ac8_Bernard%20Bouton%20the%20New%20Thinker.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12092de75c2aa096b130_computer%20obsessed.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1216b93ffd034f91dfe2_Javad%20Takjoo-IRAN%20%20(1).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1216c17524a0c37135ef_Javad%20Takjoo-IRAN%20%20(2).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1216051504dcc54255d0_Javad%20Takjoo-IRAN%20%20(3).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1221e2326333785e389e_liu-qiang-china-no%20title%20.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e122b0824853a3392b9d7_Mile%20Mancevski.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e123a72bbf01359f5a2bf_Zhaleh%20Yoosefinezhad%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e123a9f2fad3fb2f6b4a4_Zhaleh%20Yoosefinezhad%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12434a4625771f22343b_Zhaleh%20Yoosefinezhad%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12435edb52eaf34abfad_Zhaleh%20Yoosefinezhad%204.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1243134c38c1d0aed2ae_Zhaleh%20Yoosefinezhad%205.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12545fffccd3743164e9_Oleksiy_Kustovsky_Ukraine_IT1.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e125472bbf003d2f5a307_Oleksiy_Kustovsky_Ukraine_IT2.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12541967bf2db5d25f52_Oleksiy_Kustovsky_Ukraine_IT3.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1254de535e512adcd85b_Oleksiy_Kustovsky_Ukraine_IT4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e126a06aa2b8473820cc0_Work%201%20Osvaldo%20Rugani%20ARGENTINA%201%20(2).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e126a1739661416fd9f03_Work%202%20Osvaldo%20Rugani%20ARGENTINA%202%20(2).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e126aa7ad3f54b2c6714f_Work%203%20Osvaldo%20Rugani%20ARGENTINA%203%20(2).jpg]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e127237a9cbd55a521fd5_Work%204Osvaldo%20Rugani%20ARGENTINA%204%20(2).jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1280051504a2f742570e_Computer%20virus.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1280ef3ca64162beb2f6_Fake%20news.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e128076e7266684b35e2e_Groping.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e128c98af82121a21dfcc_DANGER-QIJINGYAN-CHINA-04.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e128c8d845a24b33e8adb_Inside%20story-QIJINGYAN-CHINA-03.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e128c37a9cb1fa7522050_Remote%20theft-QIJINGYAN-CHINA-02.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e128ccc9f7adc9e034f7a_Security-QIJINGYAN-CHINA-01.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e128c2918838daee1b240_Way-QIJINGYAN-CHINA-05.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e129a1739660a66fd9fb4_Raed%20khalil-Syria_01.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e129a4a4625699f22352e_Raed%20khalil-Syria_02.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e129acb00f165460d3ccc_Raed%20khalil-Syria_03.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e129a72bbf058fbf5a578_Raed%20khalil-Syria_04.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e129aaa2fe1fe72450fdd_Raed%20khalil-Syria_05.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12a9f1be88432d6e9bcb_Saeed%20Sadeghi%20-%20Iran%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12a976e7268bcab35f45_Saeed%20Sadeghi%20-%20Iran%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12a9cb00f1238e0d3cf8_Saeed%20Sadeghi%20-%20Iran%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12a9219e96f3c6929d9d_Saeed%20Sadeghi%20-%20Iran%204.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12a90db05b26af544f21_Saeed%20Sadeghi%20-%20Iran%205.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12bcc02f055dcb2fefd0_Slobodan%20Butir-Croatia-02.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12bc4e0ef5c5b336d8fe_Slobodan%20Butir-Croatia-03.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12bccb00f13c860d3d27_Slobodan%20Butir-Croatia-05.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12c3cd22fa523be2017e_Slobodan%20Butir-Croatia-06.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12c3747fe71f4332402b_Slobodan%20Butir-Croatia-08.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12c39f0a7e7407f88562_Slobodan%20Butir-Croatia-09.jpg]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12d730b1d3ca811e8d3f_Atefeh%20Yaryan%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12d7dd57f2234bd7546e_Atefeh%20Yaryan%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12d77e186066a9a2680e_Atefeh%20Yaryan%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12d7bf383e1d42b148c9_Atefeh%20Yaryan%204.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12d7ef3ca62defbeb4ee_Atefeh%20Yaryan%205.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12e24dcb0917851325b4_Lan%20Bo%20-%20China.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12f64a462529ce223674_YU%20Shih%20Sun-Image062613.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e12f5c02f0534942ff1d6_YU%20Shih%20Sun-Image062746.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e130617396657f2fda0e5_2021-07-01%2013_09_14-Vasiliy%20Alexandrov%20-%20Google%20Drive.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1306cc9f7a738a035449_2021-07-01%2013_10_20-Vasiliy%20Alexandrov%20-%20Google%20Drive.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e13069f2fad5f12f6b8f2_2021-07-01%2013_10_45-Vasiliy%20Alexandrov%20-%20Google%20Drive.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1306f1be8820516ea23d_2021-07-01%2013_11_15-Vasiliy%20Alexandrov%20-%20Google%20Drive.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e13159f0a7e39a6f88671_Vitaly%20Bondar%E2%80%93Belarus-01.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1315219e96494492a50c_Vitaly%20Bondar%E2%80%93Belarus-02.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e132ac9c054395b048c3f_Look%20at%20each%20other%E5%AF%B9%E8%A7%86.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e132a22283f4fdacddb3c_melt.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e132a37a9cbb64c5222cf_%E5%9B%9E%E8%BD%A6.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e132a0515043551425c4e_%E6%B7%B1%E6%B8%8A.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e132a5ff7376675020ce4_%E6%B8%85%E9%99%A4.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e133c7d3a679a3519c0cc_Yang%20%20Lijie-China-01.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e133c0db05b3bde5454b0_Yang%20%20Lijie-China-02.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e133c40363156a9abc7e9_Yang%20%20Lijie-China-03.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e133c2e54891b30f1fa1a_Yang%20%20Lijie-China-04.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e133c4dcb092cc913346a_Yang%20%20Lijie-China-05.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e134b4e0ef53a6e36e5dd_%E3%80%8A%E5%8F%98%E3%80%8B%E9%9D%92%E5%B2%9B%E6%B1%9F%E8%A5%BF%E8%B7%AF151%E5%8F%B7%E4%B8%80%E5%8D%95%E5%85%83602%E5%AE%A4%E6%89%8B%E6%9C%BA13969871605.jpg]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e13724589840dd900a110_%E3%80%8A%E6%96%B0%E2%80%9C%E7%8C%9B%E8%99%8E%E2%80%9D%E4%B8%8B%E5%B1%B1%E3%80%8B%E6%BC%AB%E7%94%BB13969871605%E6%9D%A8%E8%89%AF%E4%B9%89%E9%9D%92%E5%B2%9B%E6%B1%9F%E8%A5%BF%E8%B7%AF151%E5%8F%B7%E4%B8%80%E5%8D%95%E5%85%83602%E5%AE%A4266071.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1372c175240a0671460b_%E3%80%8A%E6%9C%BA%E4%B8%8D%E5%8F%AF%E5%A4%B1%E3%80%8B%E6%9D%A8%E8%89%AF%E4%B9%89%E4%BD%9C%E9%9D%92%E5%B2%9B%E6%B1%9F%E8%A5%BF%E8%B7%AF151%E5%8F%B7%E4%B8%80%E5%8D%95%E5%85%83602%E5%AE%A4%E9%82%AE%E7%BC%96266071%E6%89%8B%E6%9C%BA13969871605.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1372a3b28467cc04fdf9_Yang%20Liang%20Yi1-602%E5%AE%A4%E6%89%8B%E6%9C%BA13969871605%E6%9D%A8%E8%89%AF%E4%B9%89.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e137276e7262e6eb36285_Yangl%20Iangyi%20-%20China%20-%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1372aa2fe1723e4512e0_Yangl%20Iangyi%20-%20China%20-%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1372aa2fe1d08d4512df_Yangl%20Iangyi%20-%20China%20-%203.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1372c56e34291c639251_Yangl%20Iangyi%20-%20China%20-%204.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e1372c56e348551639250_Yangl%20Iangyi%20-%20China%20-%205.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e13c54036312fdeabcddc_Zhao%20Yunsheng%20Hi%201.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e13c5cb00f139840d47b6_Zhao%20Yunsheng%20Hi%202.jpg; https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/630e13c65bff2a46957f9375_Zhao%20Yunsheng%20Hi%203.jpg]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[cloud-computing]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[What is Cloud Computing, and Why Do You Need It?]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[cloud-computing]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e22]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:07 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 17 2023 12:08:40 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[What Is Cloud Computing? Definition, Types and Examples]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Discover everything you need to know about cloud computing - from its definition to types and examples of how it's used in the real world. ]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[33]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>In today's fast-paced digital world, businesses and individuals constantly look for ways to manage and store data more efficiently. Enter cloud computing, a transformative technology that has revolutionised how we process and store information. But what exactly is cloud computing, and how can it benefit you or your business? In this blog, we will delve into the definition of cloud computing, explore its various types, and discuss its many uses.</p><h2>What is cloud computing?</h2><p>Cloud computing refers to delivering computing services over the Internet, often called "the cloud." These services include storage, processing power, databases, software, analytics, and artificial intelligence. By utilising cloud computing, businesses and individuals can access these services on demand, paying only for the resources they use. This eliminates costly infrastructure investments and allows for greater flexibility and scalability.</p><p>Read more: <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/windows-365-in-the-cloud"><strong>Windows 365: In the Cloud</strong></a></p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/64197dda6231775813d913de_cloud-services-types.webp"></div></figure><h2>What are the three main types of cloud computing?</h2><p>Various types of cloud computing have emerged to cater to the unique needs of different users. There are three primary types of cloud computing: public, private, and hybrid. Keep reading to learn more about their features, advantages, and drawbacks, helping you decide on the right cloud solution for your needs.</p><h3>Public cloud</h3><p>The public cloud is a cloud computing service offered by third-party providers over the Internet. In this model, providers rent out computing resources, such as virtual machines, storage, and applications, to multiple users (also known as tenants) on a shared infrastructure.</p><h4>Advantages:</h4><ul><li><strong>Cost-effective:</strong>&nbsp;Public cloud users only pay for the resources they consume, which leads to reduced infrastructure and maintenance costs.</li><li><strong>Scalability:</strong>&nbsp;Users can quickly scale up or down their resources based on demand.</li><li><strong>Flexibility:</strong>&nbsp;Public cloud providers offer various services and tools, catering to different use cases.</li></ul><h4>Drawbacks:</h4><ul><li><strong>Security concerns:</strong>&nbsp;As users share resources in a multi-tenant environment, data security and privacy can be a concern for some businesses.</li><li><strong>Limited customisation:</strong>&nbsp;Public cloud services may not be flexible enough for organisations with unique or complex infrastructure requirements.</li></ul><h3>Private cloud</h3><p>A private cloud is a dedicated cloud computing environment that caters to the needs of a single organisation. The infrastructure, resources, and services can be managed by the organisation or a third-party provider. Private clouds can be deployed on-premises or hosted off-site.</p><h4>Advantages:</h4><ul><li><strong>Enhanced security:</strong>&nbsp;Private clouds provide a higher level of security compared to public clouds, as resources and infrastructure are not shared with other users.</li><li><strong>Customisation:</strong>&nbsp;Organisations have greater control over their environment, allowing for tailored solutions and configurations to meet specific needs.</li><li><strong>Compliance:</strong>&nbsp;Private clouds are ideal for organisations with strict regulatory requirements or sensitive data.</li></ul><h4>Drawbacks:</h4><ul><li><strong>Higher costs:</strong>&nbsp;Establishing and maintaining a private cloud requires significant upfront investment and ongoing expenses.</li><li><strong>Limited scalability:&nbsp;</strong>Scaling resources in a private cloud can be more challenging compared to public clouds due to dedicated infrastructures.</li></ul><h3>Hybrid cloud</h3><p>A hybrid cloud is a combination of public and private cloud environments. This model allows organisations to leverage the best of both worlds by deploying workloads and applications across both public and private clouds based on their specific requirements.</p><h4>Advantages:</h4><ul><li><strong>Flexibility:</strong>&nbsp;Hybrid cloud enables organisations to take advantage of the cost savings and scalability of public clouds while maintaining the security and customisation of private clouds.</li><li><strong>Improved resource optimisation:</strong>&nbsp;Organisations can allocate resources more effectively by deploying workloads where they are best suited.</li><li><strong>Enhanced business continuity</strong>: The hybrid approach allows organisations to distribute workloads across multiple environments, minimising the risk of downtime and data loss.</li></ul><h4>Drawbacks:</h4><ul><li><strong>Complexity:</strong>&nbsp;Managing and integrating multiple cloud environments can be challenging, often requiring advanced technical expertise and additional tools.</li><li><strong>Data transfer costs:</strong>&nbsp;Moving data between public and private clouds can result in additional costs, particularly when transferring large amounts of data.</li></ul><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/64197c1f82d66c7e37b2794c_cloud-computing-types.webp"></div></figure><h2>The main types of cloud services with example</h2><p>The cloud computing landscape has expanded rapidly in recent years, offering businesses and individuals a range of services to streamline operations, reduce costs, and improve flexibility. Among the many types of cloud services available, three categories stand out: Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS), Platform as a Service (PaaS), and Software as a Service (SaaS). We will explore these three cloud service models, providing examples for each to help you better understand their benefits and applications.</p><h3>Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS)</h3><p> <a href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/cloud-computing-dictionary/what-is-iaas#:~:text=Infrastructure%20as%20a%20service%20(IaaS,(PaaS)%2C%20and%20serverless.">IaaS</a>is the most fundamental cloud service model, providing virtualised computing resources over the Internet. It offers scalable and on-demand infrastructure, such as virtual machines (VMs), storage, and networking. With IaaS, users can quickly deploy and manage their virtual infrastructure without the need for costly physical hardware or data centre space.</p><h4>Examples of IaaS providers:</h4><ul><li><strong>Amazon Web Services (AWS)</strong>&nbsp;is a leading IaaS provider offering a wide range of cloud services, including Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) for virtual servers, Amazon Simple Storage Service (S3) for scalable storage, and Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) for networking.</li><li><strong>Microsoft Azure</strong>&nbsp;is another major IaaS provider, offering Virtual Machines, Blob Storage, and Virtual Networks. It also supports a variety of operating systems and programming languages, making it suitable for various business needs.</li></ul><h3>&nbsp;Platform as a Service (PaaS)</h3><p>PaaS is a cloud service model that provides a platform for developers to build, deploy, and manage applications without worrying about the underlying infrastructure. It includes tools and services for application development, such as runtime environments, databases, and middleware. PaaS simplifies the development process, allowing developers to focus on writing code and delivering features instead of managing infrastructure.</p><h4>Examples of PaaS providers:</h4><ul><li><strong>Google App Engine&nbsp;</strong>is a fully managed PaaS platform that supports various programming languages, including Python, Java, and Go. It automates the deployment and scaling of applications, allowing developers to focus on building high-quality applications without worrying about infrastructure management.</li><li><strong>Heroku</strong>&nbsp;is another popular PaaS platform that simplifies application deployment and scaling. It supports multiple programming languages, such as Ruby, Node.js, and PHP, and offers a range of add-on services, including databases, caching, and monitoring tools.</li></ul><h3>&nbsp;Software as a Service (SaaS)</h3><p>SaaS is a cloud service model that delivers software applications over the Internet on a subscription basis. SaaS providers host and manage the software, taking care of updates, maintenance, and security, allowing users to access the applications through a web browser without the need for installation or local storage.</p><h4>Examples of SaaS providers:</h4><ul><li><strong>Salesforce,</strong>&nbsp;a pioneer in the SaaS industry, offers customer relationship management (CRM) software that helps businesses manage sales, customer service, and marketing activities. Salesforce's cloud-based platform allows users to access their data from anywhere, making it an essential tool for modern businesses.</li><li><strong>Slack</strong>&nbsp;is a popular team collaboration and communication platform. It provides a centralised location for teams to share messages, files, and documents. With Slack's SaaS model, users can access their conversations from any device, streamlining communication and promoting productivity.</li><li><strong>Google Workspace</strong>, formerly known as G Suite, offers cloud-based productivity and collaboration tools, including Gmail, Google Docs, Google Sheets, and Google Slides. Users can access these applications from any device, collaborate in real time, and store files securely in the cloud.</li></ul><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/64197c318d6355512e6c2953_cloud-computing-uses.webp"></div></figure><h2>Benefits of cloud computing</h2><p>Here are some key benefits of adopting cloud computing for both individuals and businesses:</p><ol><li><strong>Cost savings</strong>: Cloud computing reduces the need for expensive hardware, software licenses, and maintenance costs. Users can scale their usage up or down based on their needs, resulting in cost savings and improved efficiency.</li><li><strong>Scalability:</strong>&nbsp;Cloud computing allows users to easily scale resources up or down depending on their requirements. This flexibility means businesses can quickly adapt to changing demands without the need for significant investments in infrastructure.</li><li><strong>Accessibility:</strong>&nbsp;Cloud-based applications and data can be accessed from anywhere with an internet connection, enabling remote work and collaboration among team members in different locations.</li><li><strong>Reliability:</strong>&nbsp;Cloud computing providers typically offer robust backup and recovery options, ensuring that your data is protected and readily available in case of hardware failures or other issues.</li><li><strong>Security:</strong>&nbsp;Many cloud providers offer advanced security features, such as data encryption and multi-factor authentication, to protect sensitive information and ensure only authorised users have access.</li></ol><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/64197cb4b2e6420ee3d2f52c_cloud-computing-benefits.webp"></div></figure><h2>What is the future of cloud computing?</h2><p>The past decade has seen cloud computing transform from a novel concept to a ubiquitous part of our daily lives. With new developments on the horizon, it's essential to take a closer look at the future of cloud computing and the exciting possibilities it holds.</p><h3>Serverless computing</h3><p>One of the most notable trends shaping the future of cloud computing is the emergence of serverless computing. This concept allows developers to focus on writing code without worrying about the underlying infrastructure. As serverless computing gains traction, it is expected to become a key enabler of new applications and services, reducing costs and increasing efficiency.</p><h3>Edge computing</h3><p>Edge computing, a distributed computing paradigm, aims to process data closer to its source. As the need for real-time data processing and low-latency applications grows, edge computing will play a crucial role in the future of cloud computing. By reducing the distance between data sources and processing points, edge computing can deliver faster response times and reduced bandwidth requirements.</p><h3>Multi-Cloud and hybrid cloud strategies</h3><p>Organisations are increasingly adopting multi-cloud and hybrid cloud strategies to leverage the unique strengths of different cloud providers. These strategies enable businesses to optimise their workloads, reduce costs, and minimise the risk of vendor lock-in. In the future, we can expect more organisations to adopt multi-cloud and hybrid cloud approaches, leading to increased competition and innovation in the market.</p><h3>AI and machine learning integration</h3><p>Artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML) are becoming increasingly important in cloud computing. In the coming years, we can expect AI and ML to play a more significant role in optimising cloud services, improving security, and enabling new applications. This integration will lead to more intelligent cloud platforms that can adapt and learn from user behaviour and provide better, more personalised experiences.</p><h3>Enhanced security and privacy</h3><p>As cloud computing continues to evolve, security and privacy will remain top concerns for users and businesses. The future of cloud computing will see advancements in encryption technologies, improved identity and access management solutions, and the implementation of zero-trust security models. These measures will help safeguard user data and ensure the continued growth of cloud computing adoption.</p><h3>Sustainable cloud computing</h3><p>With environmental concerns becoming more urgent, the demand for sustainable cloud computing is growing. Data centres consume vast amounts of energy, and the future of cloud computing will need to address this issue. We can expect innovative approaches, such as energy-efficient data centres, carbon offset programs, and the use of renewable energy sources, to become more common in the cloud computing industry.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a306464d9a93f08544bb94_cloud-computing.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a306464d9a93f08544bb94_cloud-computing.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[computer-security-day]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[Computer Security Day]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[computer-security-day]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60dc3]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:00 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Thu Oct 12 2023 15:23:02 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[10 Tips to Keep Your computer Secure]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[We have compiled a simple list of basic but essential tips to help you safeguard your computer and sensitive information.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[12]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>Computer Security Day is held yearly on the 30th of November to raise awareness for digital security. In a world where information has become our most valuable asset, preserving it personally and professionally is pivotal. We have put together a simple list of basic but essential tips to help you<strong>safeguard</strong>your computer and sensitive information.</p><h2><strong>Easy tips to keep your computer safe</strong></h2><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2cf6519693f8eb3ca50_Computer-security-day.png"></div></figure><p>TechVertu can help your company to protect your most valuable asset &ndash; information. Our team of IT experts will make sure that your data and systems are safe and can be fully recovered in case of disaster. Request your free no obligation quote today or just call us for a friendly chat.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a31300d0fd545124c9039d_qr-code.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a31300d0fd545124c9039d_qr-code.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[techvertu-donating-computers-to-local-charities]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[Computers Donated to Local Charities]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[computers-donated-to-local-charities]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e1c]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:05 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Thu Oct 12 2023 15:19:58 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Donating Computers and IT equipment to local charities ]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[TechVertu has now donated all available computers and IT equipment to local causes around Essex. ]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[22]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>&zwj;TechVertu has now donated all available IT equipment to local causes around Essex. Remember that the business was asking for local charities and meritable causes to apply for their chance to get free used computers, all in working condition.</p><p>A total of 11 institutions and charities have now received almost four dozen second-hand laptop and desktop computers donated by the IT agency based in Grays. &ldquo;We received several requests, many more than we were initially expecting. Unfortunately, we couldn&rsquo;t help everyone, but we&rsquo;ve tried our best to fulfil the needs of as many institutions as possible&rdquo;, explains Hadi Marashy, TechVertu&rsquo;s Managing Director.</p><p>The institutions which received the donated IT equipment were spread across Grays, Basildon, Tilbury, Chelmsford, Clacton-on-Sea and Saffron Walden. TechVertu&rsquo;s team tried to visit as many institutions as possible to deliver the computers personally.&nbsp;</p><p>&ldquo;It was an enriching experience as we could see, first-hand, what type of difference our donations are going to make&rdquo;, Hadi Marashy says.&nbsp;</p><p>The&nbsp; <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/">IT company</a>, part of the John F Hunt Group, expects to have more used equipment available soon and is planning to carry out other similar campaigns before summer.</p><p>&zwj;<strong>Meet the institutions:</strong></p><ul><li><strong>Thurrock&rsquo;s TNF team</strong>&ndash; Talking Newspaper Federation - sends out local news mp3 files on USB sticks to blind and partially sighted residents of Thurrock each week.</li></ul><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e217f4a375f6cf808f_TNF-355x355.jpeg"></div></figure><ul><li><strong>Support 4 Sight</strong>assists people with sight loss, their carers and families. Expert staff and trained volunteers help people coming to terms with losing their sight and to cope long term with the social, emotional and practical issues that they face living with sight loss.</li><li><strong>The Thurrock group of Deadblind UK</strong>supports people with dual sensory loss, helping them to live the lives they want as independently as possible. Our donations will allow those amazing professionals to visit more isolated members throughout Essex and help with their digital inclusion.</li><li>Some of our tech donations are now here &ndash; at<strong>St Helena Hospice</strong>, in Chelmsford. This institution helps local people face incurable illness and bereavements, supporting them and their families, friends and carers!</li></ul><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e25a5caca43c7b37f9_St-Helena-355x355.jpeg"></div></figure><ul><li><strong>Signpost Greenstead</strong>in Chelmsford offers a wide range of services, empowering people to move into sustainable employment, education and training opportunities. And therefore, it massively relies on IT equipment, which people can access free of charge.</li></ul><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e2b9c5c19addf894f5_Singpost-355x355.jpeg"></div></figure><ul><li><strong>Bright Lives</strong>is an organisation that supports people with additional learning needs and helps educate them to learn how to live independently into society. We&rsquo;ve donated some of our computers to their development centre in Colchester so they can carry out this fantastic work.</li><li><strong>Stepping Stones Play &amp; Learn Group</strong>is an integrated nursery for mainstream children and children with additional needs. They have a tots group for babies with special needs, and an integrated nursery to give both mainstream children and children with additional needs the chance to play and learn together.</li></ul><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e380f7785b63860548_Stepping-Stones-355x355.jpeg"></div></figure><ul><li><strong>The Citizens Advice Tendring</strong>in Chelmsford provides free, confidential and impartial advice and campaign on big issues affecting people's lives. Many of their PC's have certainly seen better days, and replacing them with the equipment donated by TechVertu should allow this team of volunteers to give a more efficient service to the local residents.</li></ul><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e2f0f8c30ea0357ff9_Tendring-CAB-e1551441474539.jpeg"></div></figure><ul><li>Happy faces after our visit to<strong>St Luke&rsquo;s Hospice</strong>, in Basildon, to donate IT equipment for both their staff and electrical shop. A special Thank You to Mark Crane, the organisation&rsquo;s Information Technology Officer, for such kind words: &ldquo;As a charity, St. Luke&rsquo;s Hospice relies on generous donations, and gifting IT equipment is incredibly helpful. It&rsquo;s important our staff are equipped with the right tools to do their jobs effectively, which includes things like working computers, so we&rsquo;re hugely grateful to TechVertu for donating their equipment to us.&rdquo;</li></ul><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e260eed20d42a59a95_St-Lukes-355x355.jpeg"></div></figure>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a30b1b1ffa4c81decc735b_giveaway-2.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a30b1b1ffa4c81decc735b_giveaway-2.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[cyber-essential-certification]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[Cyber Essentials Certification]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[cyber-essentials-certification]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e8c]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:12 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 17 2023 09:18:01 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Cyber Essentials Certification - TechVertu]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[As a licensed Certification Body, we can help you implement and achieve the Cyber Essentials and Cyber Essentials PLUS certifications.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[44]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>As a licensed Certification Body, we can help you implement and achieve the<strong>Cyber Essentials and Cyber Essentials PLUS certifications</strong>. &zwj;</p><h2><strong>What is Cyber Essentials?</strong></h2><p> <a href="https://www.ncsc.gov.uk/">The National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC)</a>administers Cyber Essentials - an affordable certification scheme that helps you defend your organisation against the most common cyber-attacks and threats.</p><p>Certification and Cyber Essentials compliance could qualify your organisation for Government contracts as well as prevent your organisation from being vulnerable to the most basic of attacks, which may lead to more in-depth and specific attacks.</p><h2>Types of Cyber Essentials Certificates</h2><p><strong>There are two types of cyber certifications to be achieved:</strong></p><p><strong>1. Cyber Essentials</strong>is a foundation level certification. This provides assurances that your organisation has controls in place to prevent exposure to 80% of common cyber threats.</p><p><strong>2. Cyber Essentials Plus</strong>is an advanced certification. A certified assessor will conduct a rigorous examination of your controls to verify that your business is protected.</p><h3>&zwj;<strong>Is this certification right for you?</strong></h3><p><strong>A Cyber Essentials Certificate</strong>is strongly recommended for your business if:</p><ul><li>An IT infrastructure is part of your business's operation</li><li>Using a computerised or online system, your business collects, stores, and uses customer or employee information</li><li>You generally want to improve the security protection of your business</li></ul><p>Once achieved, we recommend renewing your certification annually. By doing so, you can maintain your certified status and make sure your <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/what-is-cybersecurity">cyber security</a>controls are continually reviewed and developed.</p><h2>&zwj;<strong>Why choose us for getting Cyber Essentials Certification?</strong></h2><p> <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/">TechVertu</a>is an accredited Certification Body with the ability to perform both Cyber Essentials and Cyber Essentials Plus assessments on your organisation.</p><p>As a trusted partner for our customers, we offer guidance and support during the whole certification process. To maximise your chances of passing on the first try, we want to ensure you are fully prepared before we conduct your assessment!</p><p>Feel free to contact one of our cyber security experts today. Call 020 3821 1119 or send an email to info@techvertu.co.uk</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1c56ada8682d5b1cf9d67_Cyber-essentials.png]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1c56ada8682d5b1cf9d67_Cyber-essentials.png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[Cyber Security]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[twitter-giveaway]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[FreebieFriday - Twitter Giveaway]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[freebiefriday-twitter-giveaway]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e18]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:03 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 10:28:40 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[FreebieFriday - Twitter Giveaway - TechVertu]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[This week, our Freebie Friday is slightly different as all the action is happening on Twitter! Read For More!]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[19]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>This week, our Freebie Friday is slightly different as all the action is happening on Twitter!</p><p>We&rsquo;re giving away a fantastic<strong>&pound;15 App Store &amp; iTunes</strong>gift voucher to a lucky winner! All you have to do is to follow our <a href="https://twitter.com/TechVertu">TechVertu twitter page</a>and share the original competition post (you can also tag a friend for good luck ?)</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2dfb254a6e84a0bf908_Copy-of-GIVEAWAY.jpeg"></div></figure><p>This FreebieFriday Giveaway is open until 23.59 pm on Monday, 11<sup>th</sup>February 2019. The lucky winner will be selected at random amongst all entries and announced on Tuesday 12<sup>th</sup>February.</p><p>Good luck!</p><p>Full Terms &amp; Conditions <a href="https://epr.ms/2ROcSbA">https://epr.ms/2ROcSbA</a></p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a30f2261605da4075eedaf_giweaway-apple-thingy.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a30f2261605da4075eedaf_giweaway-apple-thingy.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[getting-it-support-at-techvertu]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[Ways of Getting Support at TechVertu]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[getting-support]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e25]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:09 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 17 2023 12:05:36 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Different Ways of Getting IT help at Techvertu]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[There are different ways of getting IT help from Techvertu. You can be in touch by Email, Call, or use our Application on your desktop. Read For More!]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[39]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>There&nbsp;are many great ways to get help from the <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/it-support">IT Support</a>team at TechVertu. You can:&nbsp;</p><ul><li>Use the TechVertu application on your desktop</li><li>Use our <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/contact-us">contact form</a></li><li>Send an email to&nbsp; <a href="mailto:support@techvertu.co.uk">support@techvertu.co.uk</a>&nbsp;</li><li>Call us on 020&nbsp;3821 1119&nbsp;</li></ul><h2><strong><em>Using the TechVertu application</em></strong></h2><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2fd117dd7c0270c5523_image-1.png"></div></figure><p>When you click on the TechVertu application, this window pops up. This is the best way to get our assistance, as you can use the simple tool to put in your contact information. You can include up to three screenshots to show us what is happening. Above all, this comes through to our system very quickly&nbsp;and we can&nbsp;even see the current status of the computer it was sent from!&nbsp;</p><h2><strong><em>Emailing&nbsp;</em></strong> <a href="mailto:support@techvertu.co.uk"><strong><em>support@techvertu.co.uk</em></strong></a>&nbsp;</h2><p>Sending us emails is another great way to get our assistance. This method takes your email and processes it into a ticket. Once processed, you will receive an email notification, letting you know that we have seen your request.</p><h2><strong><em>Calling 0203 821 1119</em></strong>&nbsp;</h2><p>If you haven&rsquo;t got access to the internet or your emails, or your request is urgent, you can call our main office number.&nbsp;Depending on which service you require, you will need to press one of the following&nbsp;numbers on your keypad:&nbsp;</p><p>Press&nbsp;1&nbsp;for support&nbsp;</p><p>Press 2 for sales&nbsp;</p><p>Press 3 for billing&nbsp;</p><p>Press 9 for other&nbsp;</p><p>Also remember to always&nbsp;use the ticket reference number&nbsp;in your email&rsquo;s subject,&nbsp;when responding to&nbsp;any of&nbsp;our emails.&nbsp;Example:&nbsp;T20200212.0001&nbsp;</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2fd9439994e939fb00d_image.png"></div></figure><p><strong>We hope this guide will help you get the best level of support we can provide.&nbsp;</strong></p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a3045a51aa5453465db854_laptop-cover.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a3045a51aa5453465db854_laptop-cover.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[how-it-support-services-can-save-your-time]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[How IT Support Can Save Your Team Time]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[how-it-support-can-save-your-team-time]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60f4c]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Wed Nov 23 2022 13:15:28 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 17 2023 10:57:32 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[3 main reasons that IT Support can save your business time]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Many leaders ignore the IT of their business until its late. Here we explore how investing in reliable IT support can help your business save valuable time.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>Many business leaders or owners ignore the IT aspect of their business until it&rsquo;s too late and mistakes are made. Especially smaller or start-up companies may think they&rsquo;re too small to need IT support. In reality, however, it is utterly false, and companies of all sizes can reap the benefits of outsourced IT support, regardless of their size. In this article we explore how investing in reliable IT support can help your organisation save valuable time.</p><h2><strong>Saves wasted time spent on training</strong></h2><p>In smaller businesses where employees must wear many hats, outsourcing your IT support can save your staff from spending too much time on training. Due to the constant emergence of new technology, the IT field requires a solid training-based focus to master and use these updated features effectively.</p><p>Read more: <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/10-factors-to-consider-when-outsourcing-it-support-services">Factors to consider when outsourcing IT support services</a></p><p>Learning how to use the latest technology can also waste valuable business time and money if you&rsquo;re outsourcing this training. As a result, having IT support providers can help minimise this expenditure, as well as the time wasted implementing and learning it since most providers will already know standard systems and can integrate new features with your existing system.</p><p>At <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk">TechVertu</a>, we know how important it is for companies to save time on aspects such as training, which is why our customised IT services are ideal for freeing up more time so companies can put it back into other parts of their business.</p><h2><strong>Instant expert advice</strong></h2><p>For businesses that outsource IT support, one of the most significant time-saving advantages is the ability to contact their support provider at any time, anywhere for support in the event of a technical malfunction.</p><p>Having IT support will help you save time employing a professional to rectify the issue and reduce the time it takes to resolve the problems. You can rely on your outsourced provider to get the job done as soon as an issue is identified, ultimately saving your company time, and avoiding downtime.</p><h2><strong>IT support puts more time back into your business</strong></h2><p>Having to deal with technical issues can be a nightmare, especially when you have a business to run and other pressing matters to take care of. With outsourced IT support, all this stress and worry can be transferred to a qualified IT professional experienced in handling such problems, so you don&rsquo;t waste valuable business time trying to resolve the issue yourself.</p><p>Enlisting IT support services, like the ones we offer here at TechVertu, enables you to put then the time you could have wasted back into your business by allocating it to areas of the company that need it!</p><p><strong>Contact us today by calling 020 3821 1119 or emailing info@techvertu.co.uk to see how our</strong> <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/it-support"><strong>IT support company</strong></a><strong>could help save you and your workforce time.</strong></p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/637e1ce9c03d73313199bc2f_blog-picture.png]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/637e1ce9c03d73313199bc2f_blog-picture.png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[how-to-get-qr-code-for-your-linkedin-profile]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[How to Get a QR Code for Your LinkedIn Profile]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[how-to-get-a-qr-code-for-your-linkedin-profile]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e21]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:07 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 17 2023 12:15:08 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[How to Get a QR Code for Your LinkedIn Profile?]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Even though LinkedIn introduced this new functionality last year, many users are still unaware of LinkedIns QR code feature. Its super handy; Read For More.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[29]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>Even though <a href="https://www.linkedin.com">LinkedIn</a>introduced this new functionality last year, many users are still unaware of LinkedIn&rsquo;s QR code feature. It&rsquo;s super handy and super trendy &ndash; what&rsquo;s not to like?</p><p>Get the QR code for your LinkedIn profile in seconds by following these easy steps. (Note: if you don&rsquo;t have it yet, you will need to download and install the LinkedIn app on your phone)</p><ul><li>Open the LinkedIn app and click on the icon located on the right-hand side of the search bar</li></ul><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e7727d016116c89ddd_image.png"></div></figure><ul><li>Select option &ldquo;My code&rdquo; (note: you may need to grant access to your camera first)</li></ul><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e7576579169c4e9d10_image-1.png"></div></figure><ul><li>You can share your QR code straight away or save it to your phone to share it later. You also have the option to share/save it with or without your profile picture. If you save it to your phone, you have a digital business card always ready to be handed out</li></ul><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e7ccc4f7a74bad8c66_image-4.png"></div></figure><ul><li>If you need to scan someone else&rsquo;s QR code, switch to the &ldquo;Scan&rdquo; tab</li></ul><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e73fd27dc4fd041373_image-3.png"></div></figure><p>These LinkedIn QR codes can be easily shared and are extremely useful, especially when attending conferences and networking events. They can also be added to websites, business cards and CVs.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a3084614b12c66e295bde2_sadasdsadasdas.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a3084614b12c66e295bde2_sadasdsadasdas.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[wipe-hard-drive]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[How to Properly Wipe a Hard Drive]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[how-to-properly-wipe-a-hard-drive]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60dc2]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:07:59 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Thu Oct 12 2023 15:24:07 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[How to Properly Wipe a Hard Drive?]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[If you want your data recovery to be impossible, the only way which guarantees absolute results would be that your hard drive to be physically destroyed.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[8]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>We make sure your data is lost forever!</p><p>If you want your data recovery to be impossible, the only way which guarantees absolute results would be that your hard drive to be physically destroyed.</p><p>We offer a range of tools that will make sure the data is gone forever by using a tandem roller, a breaker or an excavator.</p><p>Browsing History. Gone!</p><p>Personal documents. Gone!</p><p>As part of our service we also offer you a video as a souvenir of your hard drive being destroyed!</p><figure><div></div></figure><p>We are an <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/">IT Company</a>based in London. We have a vast range of experience relating to IT and Networking, that we have decided to share with everyone to help out and share tips.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a315c85888abd30f509270_wipe-harddrive.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a315c85888abd30f509270_wipe-harddrive.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[identifying-spam-emails]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[Identifying Spam Emails]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[identifying-spam]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e20]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:07 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 08:39:47 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[How to Identify & Prevent Spam Emails? | TechVertu]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[One of the most common ways personal data gets leaked, or viruses get onto a computer, is through spam emails. Here, we discuss how you can identify Spam Emails]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[31]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>One of the most common ways personal data gets leaked, or viruses get onto a computer, is through spam emails. In these emails, opening files sent as attachments or clicking on hyperlinks to unknown websites should be avoided at all costs, otherwise malware could do serious damage to not just your computer, but all your business&rsquo; network.</p><p>Another common type of deceptive email is called Spoofing. This means that someone can pose as one of your colleagues; you will see that the name on the email is the same, but if you look closer at the originating email address, you might find it is merely made to look very similar, with really minor changes. It is best to always question emails coming in requesting bank transfers to cover business costs, even if it comes from someone you believe to be legitimate.</p><p>Hacked email accounts can be very dangerous. If an outside source gains access to a colleague&rsquo;s account and sends something you deem to be suspicious, it is best you try to contact this person through some other means, as opposed to email. If the email has been infiltrated it could send links to even more people, compromising everyone.</p><p>If you believe you have received a spam email, the first thing to do is to check who is sending you the email; don&rsquo;t open anything you are suspicious of. If it is Spam and you are still unsure, contact your IT support team to let them know. They can block the sender or isolate any hacked accounts, as well as perform virus scans on your system to ensure it is clean of malware.</p><p>We have a team of IT experts always available to help you and your teams deal with annoying and time-consuming IT issues. To find out more about our services and how we can help your business to become more productive, <a href="/contact-us">contact us</a>for a friendly chat.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a307944fb9554a9b9655e3_mailwarning.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a307944fb9554a9b9655e3_mailwarning.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[it-support-for-businesses]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[IT Support for Businesses  Take Control of Your Passwords]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[it-support-for-businesses-take-control-of-your-passwords]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e27]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:10 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 10:29:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Take Control of Your Passwords with IT Support - TechVertu]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[TechVertus IT support and password management service gives you complete peace of mind - take control of your passwords.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[45]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>With over 95% of cybersecurity breaches being put down to human error, it is imperative that every business has a secure password policy to manage logins and passwords. TechVertu&rsquo;s IT support and password management service gives you complete peace of mind - take control of your passwords with a vault that can set complex and discrete passwords and a team of IT experts to support you all the way!</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b33d3fd27d630b0414d8_IT-SUPPORT-FOR-BUSINESSES-TAKE-CONTROL-OF-YOUR-PASSWORDS-BLOG-IMAGE-1024x724.png"></div></figure><p>Passwords are typically the first line of defence guarding critical data. Research has found that the average user has over a dozen different passwords to remember at any given time. To cope, often weak and repeated passwords are used - compromising a business&rsquo;s security and frequently resulting in exploitation from attackers. Password managers offer a secure way of coping with password overload, ensuring passwords are strong and secure, eminently reducing the risk of cybercrime.</p><h2><strong>How can TechVert help you?</strong></h2><p>TechVertu can help your company to protect your most valuable asset &ndash; information. Our team of IT experts will make sure that your data and systems are safe. We can help you create and implement your complete IT security policy &ndash; with our password management service as part of your <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/it-support">IT support package</a>.</p><p>If you would like to find out more, do not hesitate to <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/contact-us"><strong>get in touch.</strong></a></p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1d040353c6f5abe7fc8b2_IT%20SUPPORT%20FOR%20BUSINESSES%20-%20TAKE%20CONTROL%20OF%20YOUR%20PASSWORDS%20icon%20image.png]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1d040353c6f5abe7fc8b2_IT%20SUPPORT%20FOR%20BUSINESSES%20-%20TAKE%20CONTROL%20OF%20YOUR%20PASSWORDS%20icon%20image.png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[Cyber Security]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[it-support-vs-data-analyst]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[IT Support Vs Data Analyst: What's the Difference?]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[it-support-vs-data-analyst]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60fcf]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Mar 02 2023 10:48:19 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 08:48:47 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[IT Support Vs Data Analyst: Top 4 Differences - TechVertu]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Data analyst and IT Support are Two of the most in-demand professions in today's work environment. Gain insight into both positions and know the differences.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[54]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>The rapid rate of innovation has increased the pace of technological change, providing numerous opportunities for those with the required abilities. <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/it-support">IT support</a>and <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Data_analysis">data analysis</a>are two roles that typically involve using computing technology; however, their focus and job responsibilities differ. Keep reading to learn more about the IT support vs. data analyst job roles.</p><p>Both IT support and data analyst jobs are vital to improving the functions of organisations, but they have distinct descriptions. In this post, we compare and contrast IT support vs. data analyst, providing comprehensive information for those interested in pursuing a career as a data analyst or an IT support specialist.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/64008b662bd1b6489581dd38_data-analyst-woman.webp"></div></figure><h2>IT support vs. data analyst job responsibilities</h2><p>IT support is a catchall word that refers to a wide variety of endeavours that must be carried out effectively to ensure the optimal operation of an information technology system. This involves installing hardware and software, diagnosing and fixing problems, configuring networks, and assisting and directing users with technical questions and concerns.</p><p>On the other hand, gathering, evaluating, and comprehending information for the benefit of companies and organisations fall within the purview of data analysts. This involves building, testing, and deploying data models, developing algorithms to analyse data, providing reports and visualisations, and constructing a data pipeline.</p><p>The two positions often collaborate on finding solutions when dealing with complex business issues. IT support specialists offer the technical knowledge and assistance required to deploy data analysis solutions. In contrast, data analysts use their capabilities to analyse data and design strategies that assist companies and organisations in making educated choices.</p><h2>IT support vs. data analyst job qualifications</h2><p>While applicants with a bachelor's degree are preferred by specific organisations, IT support technicians are typically required to have at least an associate degree in computer science or a discipline closely linked to it. In most cases, a bachelor's degree is required of data analysts as well; however, the specifics of their study area might differ.&nbsp;</p><p>Many data analysts have academic backgrounds in mathematics, statistics, or computer science. Nonetheless, some data analysts may hold degrees in other fields, mainly if most of their educational background consisted of courses focused on data, such as those in economics or psychology.</p><h2>IT support vs. data analyst working conditions</h2><p>Professionals assisting with information technology and analysing data often work in offices. Yet, the atmosphere in which people operate is determined by the requirements of their employers.</p><p>For instance, a vast corporation's information technology department might work together to find innovative solutions for any issues and challenges. On the other hand, a small firm could have one or two IT team members responsible for handling difficulties for the whole organisation.</p><p><strong>IT support specialists</strong>often work during standard business hours; however, certain businesses demand them to be accessible around the clock, seven days a week.</p><p>This is because many IT-related problems arise outside of standard business hours. Data analysts work throughout regular business hours most of the time; nevertheless, some companies anticipate them to put in extra hours if it is required to do so.</p><p>These positions demand a high level of education and relevant professional experience. Moreover, candidates for both positions should have a solid grasp of computer systems and networks and the ability to adapt to emerging technology swiftly.</p><p>Read more: <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/types-of-it-support-services"><strong>Five Types of IT Support Services for Every Business</strong></a></p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/64008b781247f205db08bf63_it-support-man.webp"></div></figure><h2>IT support vs. data analyst capabilities</h2><p>Support for Information Technology (IT) and Data Analysis are two of the most crucial and in-demand professions in today's work environment. Each role needs different skills, but they also have specific characteristics in common.</p><p>Knowledge of computers and other forms of technology is necessary if one aspires to work in information technology support. IT Support specialists need to be able to diagnose and fix problems with both hardware and software problems and network and security issues.</p><p>Moreover, they should be able to install and configure systems and have a solid grasp of the architecture of computer systems. Certifications and practical experience gained on the job will be used to develop one's technical talents even further.</p><p>In addition to having technical expertise, people who work in IT Support need to be able to interact effectively with clients and other team members and deliver clear and precise instructions. In addition, they should be capable of working individually and as part of a team and have good problem-solving and critical-thinking abilities.</p><p>Data analysts need a unique set of yet comparable talents. The ability to perform well in mathematics and an in-depth understanding of statistical concepts are essential qualifications for data analysts. Furthermore, they need to have a solid comprehension of data analysis and be competent in data mining and modification.</p><p>Last but not least, data analysts need to be able to effectively explain the obtained results to the other members of their team as well as to customers. They should also be capable of working individually and collaboratively and possess good problem-solving and analytical abilities. In addition, they should be able to work autonomously.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/64008b8bdcf3487a0d062930_computer-science-woman.webp"></div></figure><h2>IT support vs. data analyst income</h2><p>The annual income for an IT support specialist is, on average, &pound;32,500, whereas the yearly compensation for a data analyst is &pound;42,500 in the United Kingdom. Both incomes are subject to change based on the kind of business you work for, your experience, and the region in which you live.</p><h2>Conclusion</h2><p>This post attempted to explain everything regarding IT Support vs. Data Analyst subject. Despite similarities, the primary emphasis and tasks of the IT support specialist and the data analyst are distinct.</p><p>The primary responsibilities of IT support specialists include providing technical support to users and diagnosing and fixing problems with software, hardware, and network infrastructure. On the other hand, data analysts must gather, organise, and analyse data to derive insights and guide business choices.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/640080f110a9c97199743ea0_Untitled%20(1024%20%C3%97%201024px)%20(6).png]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/640080f110a9c97199743ea0_Untitled%20(1024%20%C3%97%201024px)%20(6).png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[key-elements-for-internal-communication-plan]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[3 Key Elements for an Internal Communications Plan]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[key-elements-for-an-internal-communications-plan]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e1d]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:05 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 08:49:36 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Internal Communications Plan - Top 3 Key Elements | TechVertu]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Learn how to create a winning internal communications plan in 3 simple steps. Achieve your business goals with effective strategies.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[28]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>Want to develop a simple but efficient internal communications plan for your company? So make sure you follow these 3 easy steps.</p><h2>3 Key Elements for an Internal Communications Plan</h2><h3><strong>1. Objectives</strong></h3><p>Clearly state your business goals. An internal communications plan is ultimately a way to achieve an organizational outcome in a quicker and more effective way. But without your team&rsquo;s help, a business plan will never succeed. So, don&rsquo;t just state what the business goals are; make sure to explain to your employees what exactly is going to be achieved and, most importantly, what&rsquo;s going to change when those objectives have been accomplished. And don&rsquo;t forget &ndash; objectives don&rsquo;t always have to be &ldquo;end of the road&rdquo; type of results; they can and shall also include smaller but rewarding goals to be met along the way.</p><h3><strong>2. Plan of action</strong></h3><p>Now that you&rsquo;ve explained to your team what you want to achieve as a company, make sure you clearly state how you plan to achieve it. Never forget &ndash; without your team, your business will never accomplish anything so make sure you involve all employees on every step of the way. Explain what&rsquo;s expected from them and also what&rsquo;s in it for them.</p><h3><strong>3. Channels of communication</strong></h3><p>Create easy ways through which employees can give their contributions, share their opinions and help achieving the business goals. And make sure they understand when and how to use those channels. Facilitating the access to communications&rsquo; tools, which will help the organisation achieving its goals, is a key element to get higher levels of engagement from your employees.</p><p>If you still need help putting together a superstar internal communications plan, make sure you get in touch with our marketing &amp; communications team for a friendly chat.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a308b614b12c511795c04b_communicate.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a308b614b12c511795c04b_communicate.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[logmein-access-your-computer-from-the-web]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[LogMeIn - How to access your work computer from the web]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[logmein-accessing-your-work-computer-from-the-web]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e24]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:09 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 10:33:33 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[LogMeIn - Accessing Your Work Computer from the Web]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[In this blog we aim to provide guidance on how to use LogMeIn to access your work computer remotely.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[41]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>In this blog we aim to provide guidance on how to use LogMeIn to access your work computer remotely.</p><h2>How to use LogMeIn to access your work computer remotely</h2><figure><div></div></figure><h3><strong>Step 1)</strong></h3><p>Open your web browser and go to <a href="https://www.logmein.com/">www.LogMeIn.com</a></p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b301b9c5c14683f8956d_image.jpeg"></div></figure><h3><strong>Step 2)</strong></h3><p>At the top-right of the web page select &ldquo;<strong>Log In</strong>&rdquo;</p><h3><strong>Step 3)</strong></h3><p>Sign in with your email address and password. If you need to recover your password, can select &ldquo;<strong>Forgot your password?</strong>&rdquo;. This will sent a recovery email to your inbox which you can use to reset your password.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b302b0f4f642974ce024_image-1.jpeg"></div></figure><h3><strong>Step 4)</strong></h3><p>From this main page you can see the computers you can access remotely. To connect to a device, you can select the name of the computer or click on the image of the screen next to it.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b302f0f8c333ea358051_image-2.jpeg"></div></figure><h3><strong>Step 5)</strong></h3><p>Once connected, under the drop-down &ldquo;<strong>Log in to</strong>&rdquo; make sure you have selected your company name, and not the name of the computer. Then type in your company Username and Password. Please ensure you are typing your full password and not your Pin.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b302e42e5f493ca978c1_image-4.jpeg"></div></figure><h3><strong>Step 6)</strong></h3><p>You have now successfully connected to your device. It is important that once you have finished you &ldquo;<strong>Sign out</strong>&rdquo; from the remote computer. This will secure your device from being accessed with your login. If you choose to shut down your computer, please note that unless someone has access to the physical device, you will not be able to power it back on.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b302f6336bc4c52aa0a1_image-3.jpeg"></div></figure><p>If at any point you have issues and are unable to proceed, feel free to <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/contact-us">contact us at TechVertu</a></p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1e7796fc6157a8ea7a087_logmein.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1e7796fc6157a8ea7a087_logmein.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[ how-to-setup-mobile-hotspot-on-android]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[How to Set Up a Mobile Hotspot on Android: A Simple Guide]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[mobile-hotspot]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e1a]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:05 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Thu Oct 26 2023 09:06:11 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Step-by-Step Guide: Setting Up a Mobile Hotspot on Android]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Learn how to create a mobile hotspot on your Android phone with our step-by-step guide. Share your internet connection effortlessly. Get connected now!]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[27]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>This simple guide will take you through how to set up a Mobile Hotspot on your Android phone.A Mobile Hotspot is when you share the internet connection from your phone to another device.There are two methods of accessing the Hotspot Settings, we will go through both here.</p><h2><strong>Method A:</strong></h2><h3>Step 1:</h3><p><strong>Slide</strong>your finger down from the top of the screen to see the setting shortcuts.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e5f0f8c33d02357ffa_2019-02-28-08_59_15-Mobile-Hotspot-3.docx-Read-Only-Word.png"></div></figure><h3>Step 2:</h3><p><strong>Slide</strong>your finger down again to see all the available shortcuts.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e5106468ea3ba29e16_2019-02-28-09_00_55-Mobile-Hotspot-3.docx-Read-Only-Word.png"></div></figure><h3>Step 3:</h3><p><strong>Hold</strong>your finger down over Mobile Hotspot rather than tapping on it to configure the settings.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e5209b450aff9505ac_2019-02-28-09_01_45-Mobile-Hotspot-3.docx-Read-Only-Word.png"></div></figure><p>If this has worked for you, you can now skip ahead to<strong>Configuring Mobile Hotspot Settings</strong>.</p><h2>Method B:</h2><h3>Step 1:</h3><p>Search for and open the<strong>Settings App</strong>on your phone. To do this, from the Home screen,<strong>Slide</strong>your finger upwards to see all of your apps. Then select<strong>Settings</strong>.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e5117dd7a2d50c54da_2019-02-28-09_02_04-Mobile-Hotspot-3.docx-Read-Only-Word.png"></div></figure><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e504f98c0b229944ac_2019-02-28-09_02_25-Mobile-Hotspot-3.docx-Read-Only-Word.png"></div></figure><h3>Step 2:</h3><p>From Settings, open<strong>Connections</strong>.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e5f33ef53902f826cd_2019-02-28-09_02_50-Mobile-Hotspot-3.docx-Read-Only-Word.png"></div></figure><h3>Step 3:</h3><p>Scroll down and open<strong>Mobile Hotspot and Tethering</strong>.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e53fd27d411d041366_2019-02-28-09_03_10-Mobile-Hotspot-3.docx-Read-Only-Word.png"></div></figure><h3>Step 4:</h3><p>From there, we want to press on the word<strong>Mobile Hotspot</strong>to configure the settings.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e5f0f8c36aec357ffb_2019-02-28-09_03_37-Mobile-Hotspot-3.docx-Read-Only-Word.png"></div></figure><h2>Configuring mobile hotspot settings:</h2><h3>Step 1:</h3><p>Now we turn<strong>ON</strong>the<strong>Mobile Hotspot</strong>by moving the slider to the right. You can see the name of your network and password, in this case<strong>Tether-Name</strong>and<strong>Password01</strong>. You can change the name of your network or password by pressing on them and entering something else.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e6344b38eb4fb09663_2019-02-28-09_11_20-Mobile-Hotspot-3.docx-Read-Only-Word.png"></div></figure><h3>Step 2:</h3><p>Now from your computer, you will be able to see your phone&rsquo;s<strong>Mobile Hotspot Name</strong>in the list of networks you can join. Once you select it enter the<strong>Password</strong>as shown on your phone and so long as your phone has a strong signal, you should have an internet connection on your computer. If it has worked, you will see the computer listed under<strong>Connected Devices</strong>.</p><p>Read more:&nbsp; <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/outlook-on-android"><strong>How to Install and Configure Outlook on Android Phone</strong></a></p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a308fa08f5592b76044a94_hotspot.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a308fa08f5592b76044a94_hotspot.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[optimise-your-website-for-voice-search]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[Optimise Your Website for Voice Search]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[optimise-your-website-for-voice-search]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60dfd]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:01 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 17 2023 12:25:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Why Optimise Your Website for Voice Search?]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[By 2020, half of the overall searches will be conducted by voice. So read this blog to understand why you should optimise your website for voice search.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[14]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2d520d99c8a7d5d0855_Voice-search-image.jpeg"></div></figure><p>Smart devices such as Amazon&rsquo;s Echo or Microsoft&rsquo;s Cortana are becoming increasingly popular. So much that several studies and companies estimate that, by 2020, half of the overall searches will be conducted by voice.</p><p>With voice search, as the name suggests, users are able to make a query and do an online search by using only their voice. Who hasn&rsquo;t yet asked a question to Siri or Alexa, right? Those type of smart devices use speech recognition to understand your question and find the best answer(s) for it.</p><p>So, how do you (still) get your company&rsquo;s website to the first page of Google and make sure it&rsquo;s found by potential customers when everything we&rsquo;ve been learning about SEO and content optimisation seems to be changing so much? Well, you need to start optimising your content for voice search too. And the sooner you start, the better.</p><p>The growth and popularity of these smart devices and new voice-based technologies also means that the way people search for information is changing too. What someone types on Google for example, is different of what people ask Alexa. And websites need to be optimised for these new voice search techniques.</p><h2>What are the main differences between traditional search and voice search?</h2><p>1. People use longer sentences. Usually, when people do text-based searches, those are based in keywords or very short sentences. For example, when you&rsquo;re looking for an IT company in London you will probably type &ldquo;IT company London&rdquo;. However, if you make a verbal query, you will most probably use a full sentence. You will say, for instance, &ldquo;Do you know any IT company in London?&rdquo;. Therefore, your website content needs to be optimised for longer key phrases.</p><p>2. The intent is more specific.Companies need to be clever and start creating content that answers specific and appropriate queries. When someone types &ldquo;logo design&rdquo;, for instance, it&rsquo;s unclear if the person is just looking to find out more about logo design as a subject or if it&rsquo;s actually looking for a company or person who can provide that type of service. With voice search though, the intent is much clearer: &ldquo;what&rsquo;s the best company to do logo design?&rdquo;, the person will possibly ask.Optimising your content to answer the queries which are more pertinent to your business&rsquo; purposes is extremely important.</p><p>3. Voice searches have a bigger local impact.Statistics show that voice searches are more likely to be used for local searches. Therefore, optimising all aspects related to your business location is also crucial for your SEO strategy.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a3121ea738325465349f70_voice-search.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a3121ea738325465349f70_voice-search.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[install-and-configure-outlook-app-on-android-phone]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[Install and Configure the Outlook App on an Android Phone]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[outlook-on-android]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e1f]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:07 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Thu Oct 26 2023 09:13:56 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[How to Install & Configure Outlook App on an Android phone]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[In this guide, we go through how to install and configure the Outlook app on an Android phone, including how to move it to the home page and sync contacts. ]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[34]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>In this guide, we go through the steps of how to install and configure the <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.microsoft.office.outlook&amp;hl=en_GB&amp;gl=US">Outlook app on an Android phone</a>, including how to move it to the home page and sync contacts.</p><p>Using Microsoft&rsquo;s own application for emails often works better than the generic mail app that comes with the phone. It is also very useful tobe able to sync business&rsquo; contacts straight to your phone when they have been synced through Office 365.</p><h2>How to Install Outlook app on an Android phone</h2><h3>&zwj;<strong>Step 1</strong></h3><p>If Outlook is not installed, open the Play Store. If it is not on the home page, slide a finger up from the bottom to open Apps.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2f2b40cd31e5fc05494_image-21.png"></div></figure><h3><strong>Step 2</strong></h3><p>From inside the Play Store tap on the<strong>search icon</strong>(the magnifying glass symbol), type in<strong>Outlook</strong>and hit<strong>Go</strong>to search for the app.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2f23fd27d5231041399_image-22-1024x386.png"></div></figure><h3><strong>Step 3</strong></h3><p>Selec<strong>t Microsoft Outlook</strong>from the<strong>Microsoft Corporation</strong>, this will open the app&rsquo;s page. From here select<strong>Install</strong>. Once finished it will change from Install to<strong>Open</strong>.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2f2727d01cd2cc89dfa_image-23-1024x306.png"></div></figure><h3><strong>Step 4</strong></h3><p>Pressing the<strong>Home button</strong>will take the phone back to the main screen. From here open up all Apps again and look for<strong>Outlook</strong>.<strong>Holding a finger over the app and sliding upwards slowly</strong>drags it from the Apps page to the main screen. This is a helpful method of moving apps around makes searching for them easier.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2f23fd27d405204139a_image-24-1024x566.png"></div></figure><h3><strong>Step 5</strong></h3><p>Open the Outlook app and select<strong>GET STARTED</strong>. Enter the<strong>email address</strong>and<strong>password</strong>.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2f22e5f243a47dc37a0_image-12-1024x376.png"></div></figure><h3><strong>Step 6</strong></h3><p>Having successfully added the account, select<strong>SKIP</strong>unless there is a need to add another account.</p><p><strong>SKIP</strong>again passed the tutorial to access the Inbox.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2f23fd27d802404139b_image-25-1024x592.png"></div></figure><h3><strong>Step 7</strong></h3><p>Now that Outlook has been set up to receive emails, we will go through the steps of how Sync contacts from Office 365.</p><p>From the Inbox, select the<strong>three lines</strong>on the top left and then the<strong>settings cog</strong>on the bottom left.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2f3f33ef5b188f827a0_image-27-1024x271.png"></div></figure><h3><strong>Step 8</strong></h3><p>Select the<strong>Office 365 account</strong>and then move the slider next to<strong>Sync contacts to the right</strong>.</p><p>In the phone&rsquo;s contacts will be displayed all of the synced contacts from Office 365.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2f350538b6db1a45640_image-28-1024x474.png"></div></figure><p>Read more: <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/mobile-hotspot"><strong>How to Set Up a Mobile Hotspot on Android: A Simple Guide</strong></a></p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a305fe7e5b1618652691a1_outlook-config.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a305fe7e5b1618652691a1_outlook-config.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[whatsapp-hijack-scam]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[Protect Yourself from the WhatsApp Hijack Scam!]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[protect-yourself-from-the-whatsapp-hijack-scam]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e70]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:12 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 17 2023 11:34:54 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Protect Yourself From The WhatsApp Hijack Scam]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Since WhatsApp's creation, the app has been no stranger to convincing scams and SMS phishing attacks. But how can you protect yourself from WhatsApp Hijack Scam]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[47]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>&zwj;<strong>With more than two billion active monthly users around the world, WhatsApp is by far the most popular messaging app. Unfortunately, since its creation 12 years ago, the app has been no stranger to convincing scams and SMS phishing attacks.</strong></p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b34050fa0306d06107ae_Whatsapp-Hijack-scam-blog-image--1024x724.png"></div></figure><h2><strong>What is the WhatsApp hijack scam?&nbsp;</strong></h2><p>The scam itself is fairly simple and unfortunately has been around for years. When you first install WhatsApp on a new device, the platform will then ask for the phone number of the account. When you enter the phone number, you will then receive a text message giving you a one-time code. Once the correct code is entered, the phone will begin to receive WhatsApp messages. With this hack in particular, the attacker uses an already hijacked account to contact a victim&rsquo;s friend/family. In their message, the attacker commonly tells the victim&rsquo;s contact that they are having issues receiving a six-digit code, and as a result had it sent to them instead and to please send it back. That six-digit code is the WhatsApp verification code for the new victim, and by sending it to their friend/family they are actually sending it to the attacker. Once done, their own WhatsApp is hijacked!</p><p>&zwj;<strong>Read More:</strong> <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/top-tips-for-improving-your-business-cyber-security"><strong>Top Tips For Improving Your Business Cyber Security</strong></a></p><h2><strong>What do the scammers do with stolen accounts?</strong></h2><p>The hijacker can message your friends/family and pretend to be you with your stolen account. A common trick is pretending that you are having a crisis and asking your contacts to send money. It also gives the hijacker your contacts' phone numbers, so they have the opportunity to continue to try the six-digit code trick with new victims. By hijacking your account, the scammer will also remain in any group chats that you are included in, where they could potentially see sensitive information.</p><h2><strong>How can you protect yourself?</strong></h2><p>According to WhatsApp, users must remain vigilant and not share the One Time Password (OTP) or SMS security code Users must remain vigilant and under no circumstances share the One Time Password or SMS security code with anybody, according to WhatsApp. For extra protection, users can also enable two-step verification to ensure complete safety. Finally, users must contact their friends or family members if they have received any suspicious messages on WhatsApp. WhatsApp has asked users to report any messages received from an unknown number in a guide you can view on their <a href="https://faq.whatsapp.com/1313491802751163/?locale=en_GB"><strong>website</strong></a>.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1cb979a8eed93c3cad42b_Protect%20yourself%20from%20the%20whatsapp%20hijack%20scam.png]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1cb979a8eed93c3cad42b_Protect%20yourself%20from%20the%20whatsapp%20hijack%20scam.png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[Cyber Security]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[techvertu-acheives-cybersecurity-certification-for-johnfhunt-group]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[TechVertu Achieves Cyber Security Certification for John F Hunt Group]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[techvertu-achieves-cyber-security-certification-for-john-f-hunt-group]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60dc5]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:01 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 10:05:40 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[John F Hunt Group Cyber Security Certification | TechVertu]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Achieving this certification means that the security measures currently in place will protect against the vast majority of common cyber attacks.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[16]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2d369eee02a49fd4efc_computer-1591018_1920.jpeg"></div></figure><p>John F Hunt Group Limited has just attained its Cyber Security Certificate, which means that all companies within the Group comply with the requirements of the Cyber Essentials Scheme. This project was led by TechVertu, an <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/it-support">IT Support</a>agency, part of the Group, which controls and oversees the IT requirements for the whole structure. The Grays-based company also offers comprehensive IT support, web design services to external clients.</p><p>&ldquo;We hope this achievement will demonstrate our commitment to cyber security and show to our customers that we, as a Group, take this matter seriously&rdquo;, says Hadi Marashy, TechVertu&rsquo;s Managing Director.</p><p>Cyber Essentials is a government backed scheme which helps to protect organisations against cyber attacks. The assessment focusses on some of the most important technical security controls identified by the government. Achieving this certification means that the security measures currently in place will protect against the vast majority of common cyber attacks. Since October 2014, it became a minimum requirement for bidding for some government contracts.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a311068cb36021e0b66e64_security-1.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a311068cb36021e0b66e64_security-1.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[techvertu-achieves-iso-certification-from-british-assessment-bureau]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[TechVertu Achieves ISO Certification from the British Assessment Bureau]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[techvertu-achieves-iso-certification-from-the-british-assessment-bureau]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e26]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:09 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 08:32:48 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[TechVertu ISO Certification - British Assessment Bureau]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[TechVertu has just achieved certification to the internationally recognised ISO 9001:2015 and ISO 27001:2013 standards, establishing it as one of the leaders.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[38]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>Essex-based <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/">IT agency</a>TechVertu has just achieved certification to the internationally recognised ISO 9001:2015 and ISO 27001:2013 standards, establishing it as one of the leaders in its field.</p><p>The independent assessments were conducted by the British Assessment Bureau and demonstrate TechVertu&rsquo;s commitment to customer service and quality in delivery, and to keeping their data, staff and premises secure.</p><p>&ldquo;We&rsquo;ve worked really hard to attain both standards and we&rsquo;re over the moon with this achievement. We hope this demonstrates to our customers and potential clients that we are committed to the highest levels of performance, customer satisfaction and continuous improvement&rdquo;, says Hadi Marashy, TechVertu&rsquo;s Managing Director.</p><h3><strong>What do these standards mean?</strong></h3><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2fa80f7783924860597_UKAS-ISO-9001-1-988x1024.jpeg"></div></figure><p><strong>ISO 9001</strong>&ndash; was first introduced in 1987 and requires organisations to demonstrate that they do what they say they do, and that they have a Quality Management System in place to ensure consistency and improvement. Certified organisations are committed to continuous improvement and are assessed to ensure progress is being maintained.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2fab0f4f651224cdfef_UKAS-ISO-27001-1-989x1024.jpeg"></div></figure><p><strong>ISO 27001</strong>- is the internationally recognised Information Security Management Standard that proves an organisation&rsquo;s commitment to the security of their customer, employee and shareholder&rsquo;s information. With ISO 27001 in place, companies are able to minimise risks to potential data security breaches and reduce errors and costs, while demonstrating credibility and trust.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a304967e5b165113264090_iso-certificates.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a304967e5b165113264090_iso-certificates.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[techvertu-donating-computers-to-local-community]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[TechVertu Donates 35 Computers to Local Community]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[techvertu-donates-35-computers-to-local-community]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60dc1]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:07:59 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 10:30:49 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Donating 35 Computers to Local Community - TechVertu]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[TechVertu has 35 desktop and laptop computers to donate to local schools and other commendable causes needing these types of equipment.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[10]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2cda508e93b94bcc589_Hadi-Marashy-Dariusz-Misiak-donation.jpeg"></div></figure><p><strong>Update - 10th December 2018 - Due to the high volume of requests, our application process is now closed. Thank you for being so understanding.</strong></p><p><strong>&zwj;</strong>TechVertu, an <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/">IT agency</a>based in Grays, has 35 desktop and laptop computers to donate to local schools, charities, and other commendable causes needing this type of equipment.</p><p>The company asks those interested in getting in touch by email or post stating how many computers they need and why. All applications must include the organisation&rsquo;s name, address and registered number if applicable; name and contact details for the person applying; and any additional information and documents to support the application (optional).</p><p>All the equipment is used, but it&rsquo;s in perfect working condition and will be donated to institutions located in Thurrock and the Essex area.</p><p>The applications can be sent by 15th January 2019 to vania.furet@techvertu.co.uk or by post to: TechVertu, London Road, Grays, Essex, RM20 4DB. TechVertu will then choose one or several institutions or causes to receive the IT equipment in the new year.</p><p>&ldquo;We don&rsquo;t want to make just a random donation; we want to feel that we&rsquo;ve made a real difference. As a small, local new business, we want to help other people and other businesses to thrive. That&rsquo;s our motto&rdquo;, says the company&rsquo;s Managing Director, Hadi Marashy.</p><p>TechVertu has launched this donation campaign to celebrate its first anniversary, just in time for Christmas. The business was born in November 2017 when the John F Hunt Group invested in a small company, at the time named Ruuz. What started almost exclusively as a central in-house hub for the group&rsquo;s day-to-day IT and marketing requirements, with only two employees, has quickly grown to a full-service technological company. Currently, with 12 members of staff, TechVertu has all the resources, time and expertise to support or fully manage the IT systems for any other businesses, and it also offers comprehensive web development services to other companies.</p><p>&ldquo;We want to grow and have a positive impact in the local economy; we want to create more jobs, stimulate innovation, provide unique services to businesses in and around Essex and develop a strong corporate social responsibility&rdquo;, Hadi Marashy states.</p><p>In a year&rsquo;s time, the business hopes to have increased the team by at least 5 new members and opened a small office in Central London to work close to some of its clients based in the city. &ldquo;Our plans are bold and ambitious but we&rsquo;re confident we have everything we need to achieve them&rdquo;.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a3205f04bb594a8f039c3c_Hadi-Marashy-Dariusz-Misiak-donation.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a3205f04bb594a8f039c3c_Hadi-Marashy-Dariusz-Misiak-donation.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[techvertu-steps-into-chessington]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[TechVertu Steps into Chessington]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[techvertu-steps-into-chessington]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e1b]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:05 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 08:50:41 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[TechVertu Steps into Chessington - Computer Donation]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce that TechVertu is expanding to Surrey. Were opening our new office in Chessington, following our recent establishment.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[26]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>We are pleased to announce that TechVertu is expanding to Surrey. We&rsquo;re opening our new office in Chessington, following our recent re-branding and establishment as a full service <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/">IT agency</a>and a unique one-stop shop for all things tech.</p><p>We offer an extensive range of IT and creative services, from IT support to digital marketing, branding and web design, which will now be also available for Surrey-based businesses of all sizes. The new office in Chessington will soon be fully functional and we&rsquo;re already recruiting to expand our team.</p><h2><strong>Computers to be donated to local community</strong></h2><p>To mark our expansion, TechVertu&rsquo;s team is donating around a dozen computers to local schools, charities or any other commendable causes located in and around Chessington/Surrey and in need of this type of equipment. We have recently run a similar donation campaign in Essex to celebrate TechVertu&rsquo;s first anniversary and donated 35 laptops and desktop computers to Essex-based institutions.</p><p>The equipment to be donated is used but it&rsquo;s in good working condition.</p><p>The company is asking those interested to get in touch by filling a <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/contact-us">Contact Us form</a>on our website - <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/">www.techvertu.co.uk</a>- by 16<sup>th</sup>June 2019.</p><p>All messages must explain why you&rsquo;d like to be considered for this donation of IT equipment and also include the organisation&rsquo;s name, address and registered number (if applicable); name and contact details for the person applying; and any other additional information to support the application.</p><p>We will then choose one or several institutions or causes to receive the IT equipment.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a309a71a21a966ba775109_new-location.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a309a71a21a966ba775109_new-location.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[first-international-cartoon-contest-held-in-uk]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[The First International IT Cartoon Competition held in the UK]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[the-first-international-it-cartoon-competition-held-in-the-uk]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e28]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:10 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 08:29:59 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[UK First International IT Cartoon Competition | TecVertu]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[TechVertu are delighted to announce their inaugural International Cartoon Contest with the subject focusing on Information Technology Challenges for Businesses]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[52]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>TechVertu are delighted to announce their inaugural International Cartoon Contest with the subject focusing on &ldquo;Information Technology Challenges for Businesses&rdquo; at its heart. Internationally recognised artists from<strong>47 countries</strong>have been invited to participate in the<strong>First International IT Cartoon Competition</strong>ever held in the UK.</p><p>Indisputably IT Support and Technology have dramatically transformed our personal and professional lives in a relatively short space of time. Businesses are highly dependent on IT and must stay updated with the latest knowledge, skills and equipment to ensure their future growth and continued client satisfaction. In addition to this fast moving world, Covid-19 has highlighted the vital role that IT plays for everyone in staying connected to enable &lsquo;business as usual&rsquo;.</p><p>This presents a wide range of new issues to businesses worldwide, with challenges such as Data Security, Cybersecurity Threats, Hijacking, Data Backup and Recovery, Remote Working, Virtual Meetings, Fast Internet Connection, Paperless operation, Spam emails, Phishing, Online Violence and Mobile phone connections, to name but a few&hellip;the list is endless!</p><p>As an innovative IT Support and Technology company, specialising in the construction industry, TechVertu knows very well the importance of increasing public awareness concerning these challenges, risks, and opportunities. We therefore believe this Cartoon Contest could communicate this vital message to the public in a simple, thought provoking, yet amusing manner.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1d1197c2a8666c4911560_Cartoon%20Contest-%20TechVertu%20blog.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1d1197c2a8666c4911560_Cartoon%20Contest-%20TechVertu%20blog.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[proactive-it-support]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[The Importance of Proactive IT Support]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[the-importance-of-proactive-it-support]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e5b]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:12 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 07:38:53 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 07:38:53 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[What is Proactive IT Support and why is it important?]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Proactive IT support consists of two main areas of expertise, effective system monitoring and strategic technology consulting. ]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[49]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b346c2130b18d8d3ced9_The-Importance-Of-Proactive-IT-Support-pic-1024x576.png"></div></figure><p>Proactive <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/it-support">IT support</a>will optimise your business performance and fuel growth, improve your customer experience, and help you outperform your competition. In order to maximise productivity and minimise downtime, it is vital to have a proactive IT support partner. At TechVertu, we pride ourselves on providing proactive, long-term technological solutions that bring genuine value to our customers.</p><h2>What is proactive IT support?</h2><p>Proactive IT support consists of two main areas of expertise, effective system monitoring and strategic technology consulting. Proactive IT will prevent problems in the first place by consistently monitoring your systems, servers, and networks to identify and solve potential issues before they arise. This will reduce the time spent rectifying IT issues and give your team more time to work on important tasks.</p><p>Furthermore, a proactive IT support provider will really invest in helping you succeed and providing you with insightful, tailored technical advice. At TechVertu, we take the time to get to know your business and its goals. Therefore, we can draw up a coherent IT roadmap that outlines all goals, budgets and timeframes related to your IT strategy. This is then reviewed often and adapted to the current needs of your business to ensure that the service we offer is tailored to what you need.</p><h2><strong>The importance of proactive and reliable IT</strong></h2><p>To ensure that your systems function effectively, your employees can work productively, and your customers receive the best possible service, it is crucial that you have reliable, effective IT support around the clock to solve daily problems, as well as proactive technology consulting services.</p><h2><strong>Tailored IT support and technology consulting with TechVertu</strong></h2><p>In order to provide the best support, your IT partner needs to understand your business's goals, challenges, and industry requirements. As a proactive IT Support provider, TechVertu will devise a strategic IT roadmap for you that has your business goals at heart. We&rsquo;ll also provide a technology audit of your current IT infrastructure, along with recommendations for improvements, predictions for ROI and other relevant outcomes.</p><p>Proactive IT support is not merely about ensuring that updates are installed, and fixes applied. A truly proactive IT Support partner anticipates your business's needs and makes recommendations to ensure your processes are optimised and your technology solutions are tailored to your specific requirements.</p><h3><strong>As a proactive IT support company, TechVertu will:</strong></h3><p>Regular monitoring and maintenance in the background, including monitoring all server event logs, ensuring correct antivirus updates and activities, monitoring backup status, firewall activity and hack/spam attacks, application services (Exchange, <a href="https://www.gov.uk/individual-savings-accounts">ISA</a>, <a href="https://www.iis.net/">IIS</a>, etc.)</p><p>By keeping everything up to date, you will not be affected by downtime, pop-ups, and reminders.</p><p>Report on device health so you are clear about how devices are performing and can make decisions about when to replace them.</p><p>Take the time to learn about your business, industry, goals, and challenges, so that we can make accurate recommendations for technology that solves problems and boosts performance.</p><p>Provide regular technology consulting services and draw up an IT roadmap that outlines the objectives, budgets, ROI, and timeframes for your <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/tech-case-studies">IT projects</a>. This is then reviewed and updated quarterly to ensure it is always in line with business objectives.</p><p>Review and report regularly on the 24/7 <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/it-support">IT support services</a>you receive from us to ensure that all end-users receive the most accurate, reliable, and effective support.</p><h2><strong>Is your IT support provider not proactive enough?</strong></h2><p>If you have realised you do not receive the level of service your business needs to optimise growth, outperform competitors, and improve the customer experience, it is time to switch to a more proactive IT partner. Contact TechVertu today!&nbsp;</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1c9c4dc4d571175ed2e3e_The-Importance-Of-Proactive-IT-Support--1024x1024.png]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1c9c4dc4d571175ed2e3e_The-Importance-Of-Proactive-IT-Support--1024x1024.png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[techvertu-international-cartoon-contest-winners]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[The Winners of TechVertu International Cartoon Contest - 2021]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[the-winners-of-techvertu-international-cartoon-contest-2021]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60ed1]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:13 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 08:33:26 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[TechVertu International Cartoon Contest Winners - 2021]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Here are the selected artworks and the artists who are the winners of the TechVertu International Cartoon Contest 2021.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[54]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>The following are the selected artworks and the artists who are<strong>the winners of the</strong> <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/"><strong>TechVertu</strong></a><strong>International Cartoon Contest 2021.</strong>TechVertu will continue promoting this unique collection of 500 IT theme cartoons across the nation to increase public awareness concerning IT and Technology threats and challenges we face in today's life.<strong>The Online Gallery is now available</strong> <a href="/blog/cartoon-contest"><strong>HERE</strong></a><strong>where the public can view the entire collection submitted for this international cartoon contest.</strong></p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b34afb44464efbddd220_Saeed-Sadeghi-662x1024.jpeg"></div></figure><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b34bb9c5c11644f89827_Mahna-Yazdani-1024x848.jpeg"></div></figure><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b34a5443a92849eb0f9f_Kazanevsky-Vladimir-1024x848.jpeg"></div></figure><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b34a65196942b7b3ccbb_SOMITAZAHRA-SETAREHASEMAN-Peoples-Choice-1024x848.jpeg"></div></figure><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b34b50fa03f0436107d5_HEIBAT-AHMADI-Peoples-Choice-662x1024.jpeg"></div></figure><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b34bccc4f75be8ad8e18_Bahram-Arjmandnia-662x1024.jpeg"></div></figure><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b34b9f779738bc40e262_SAEED-SADEGHI-Peoples-Choice-662x1024.jpeg"></div></figure><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b34b8db6e6b908b3d99e_Raed-Khalil-1024x852.jpeg"></div></figure><p><strong>The Online Gallery is now available</strong> <a href="/blog/cartoon-contest"><strong>HERE</strong></a><strong>where the public can view the entire collection submitted for this international cartoon contest.</strong></p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1bd31be16d91c6de92bb4_Cartoon-Contest-Winners-1024x936.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1bd31be16d91c6de92bb4_Cartoon-Contest-Winners-1024x936.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[improving-business-cybersecurity]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[Top Tips For Improving Your Business Cyber Security]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[top-tips-for-improving-your-business-cyber-security]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60ea4]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:12 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 08:35:47 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Improve Your Business Cyber Security: Top 6 Tips | TechVertu]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Businesses, especially remote workers, need to update their cyber security occasionally. Check out these tips for improving your business cyber security.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[48]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>The faster technology changes, the faster users and businesses need to update their <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/what-is-cybersecurity">cyber security</a>. This key issue has been further affected by the Covid 19 pandemic, in which remote working has become a standard for employees in many organisations, with integration and flexibility among cyber security hot topics for home workers. <img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b344e42e5f0166a97ad6_Top-tips-for-improving-your-business-cyber-security-1024x576.png"></p><h2><strong>Remote working brings new threats</strong></h2><p>Cyber threats often appear in tandem with innovative working practices. People have always worked from home, but not in the numbers seen during the Coronavirus pandemic, and not using systems traditionally reserved for the workplace, such as call centres. Threats take many forms, including malware, toll fraud, and network targeting, as cyber criminals search for protection gaps. In addition to disruption and potential business losses, most organisations are also concerned about their legal compliance with GDPR legislation, other regulations, and government requirements.</p><h2><strong>Multi-Factor Authentication</strong></h2><p> <a href="https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/topic/what-is-multifactor-authentication-e5e39437-121c-be60-d123-eda06bddf661">MFA or multi-factor authentication</a>has always been considered an additional layer of security, but nowadays it is becoming much more of a norm. More often, this two-stage process is already commonplace for many people when they access their online banking or social media accounts. MFA is now a must for any business - using two or more simple verification steps to gain online access. This is typically a text with a code on a mobile phone after the username and password are entered. MFA is one of the easiest and most effective ways to protect any business or organisation.</p><h2><strong>Managing security updates</strong></h2><p>Make no mistake, hackers and cybercriminals can easily keep pace with key decision-makers in new security software to ensure that applications are regularly updated, and patches are implemented when needed. The best way to do this is to thoroughly monitor and evaluate risks to protect data, thereby generating revenue and reputation. Old apps are risky and dangerous, and easy to overlook on outdated servers and workstations. The current trend for remote working means system audits depend on all devices and staff connected to the office network.</p><h2><strong>Dark web audits</strong></h2><p>Most people are becoming increasingly familiar with the dark web, which refers to the subterranean world of the Internet, full of illicit materials including usernames and passwords, credit card information, and medical data, all available to cybercriminals. A recent dark web survey revealed over 15 billion stolen logins from more than 100,000 security breaches. For a dark web audit, specialist knowledge and access are usually required. This can be a valuable process, as it allows companies and organisations to find out which key information is available for sale and where that data comes from. The emphasis on vulnerable information enables internal changes and increased security measures.</p><h2><strong>Anti-malware</strong></h2><p>The most effective and comprehensive option to protect against malware threats is to use a cloud-based solution that is centralised and protects all devices. When purchasing malware protection, it is important to focus on key features, including: anti-ransomware, global blacklisting, on-access scanning, endpoint software firewall control, endpoint drive encryption management, external device controls, auto-update of the device itself and pattern files.</p><h2><strong>Protocols and best practices</strong></h2><p>The best way to protect yourself from cybercrime is to write a policy that covers new and existing devices with regular maintenance, updates, reviews, and stress tests. Establishing a comprehensive system of protection does not have to be costly or difficult and gives businesses peace of mind. Use protocols and checklists for new devices and updates. Undergo evaluation reviews to test that the security is working and fit for purpose. Always use a key business change or major technological developments or upgrades as a trigger to review procedures.</p><h3><strong>About TechVertu</strong></h3><p>Whether you require <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/fully-managed-it-support">fully managed IT Support</a>or want to complement your internal IT Support team, our IT specialists will deliver expert, fast, and reliable IT Support services tailored to your requirements. TechVertu's team of proactive and responsive IT experts is united by one common goal: to offer you an exceptional customer experience.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1cabae937752f380ad449_Top-tips-for-improving-your-business-cyber-security-icon.png]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1cabae937752f380ad449_Top-tips-for-improving-your-business-cyber-security-icon.png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[two-factor-authentication-for-microsoft-office-365]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[Two-Factor Authentication Guide for Microsoft Office 365]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[two-factor-authentication-guide]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e19]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:04 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 17 2023 12:24:50 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Setup Two-Factor Authentication for Microsoft 365]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[This guide will teach you how to setup two-factor authentication for Microsoft office 365. Read for More!]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[21]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>To setup two-factor authentication for Microsoft office 365, you will need to follow the below steps:</p><h2>How to setup two-factor authentication for Microsoft 365</h2><h3>1. Sign in to Office 365</h3><p> <a href="https://www.office.com/">Sign in to Office 365</a>with your work or school account with your password like you normally do. <img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e1f33ef527e7f826c3_Sign-in-box.jpeg"></p><h3>2. The account verification message shows up</h3><p>After you choose<strong>Sign in</strong>, you'll see this page: <img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e1b254a6306c0bf912_Office-365-box.jpeg"></p><h3>3. Choose<strong>Set it up now</strong>.</h3><h3>4. Select your authentication method</h3><p>Select your authentication method and then follow the prompts on the page. For Example, here we add a UK Mobile number <img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e19f7797bbce40e109_062217_1736_Office365Mu8.png"></p><h3>5. After you verify your alternate contact method, choose<strong>Next</strong>.</h3><h3>6. You will receive an app password</h3><p>You will receive an app password that you can use with your email applications. Choose the copy icon to copy the password to your clipboard. You won't need to memorize this password <img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e1f0f8c36543357ff0_Verification-box.jpeg"></p><h3>7. The next time you sign in to Office 365, you'll be prompted to enter the code</h3><p>Once you complete the instructions to specify how you want to receive your verification code, the next time you sign in to <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/microsoft-office-365">Office 365</a>, you'll be prompted to enter the code that is sent to you by text message, phone call, etc. If you need a new code, you can refresh the page by pressing F5. <img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2e18db6e65818b3d792_1_T4ZY3p_fvgMnGbd4I9BfCA.png"></p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a30e99a2d899fc5a56807f_2step-veri.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a30e99a2d899fc5a56807f_2step-veri.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[five-types-of-it-support-services]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[Five Types of IT Support Services for Every Business]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[types-of-it-support-services]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60fce]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Tue Jan 24 2023 14:55:26 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 17 2023 10:38:45 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[5 Types of IT Support Services for Every Business]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Maximize IT support for your business. Learn why and how different types of IT Support services can help your company grow.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[53]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>In today's world, IT support is an essential part of any modern business. The reality is that companies rely on technology to succeed, and thus, the ability to manage IT processes is a must. This article will discuss the best types of IT support services and how your business can use them.</p><h2>Five popular types of IT support</h2><p>There are many <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/it-support">IT support services</a>available, from network support to security, and it can take time to figure out which services you need. Here are the most popular types of IT support that could benefit your company.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/63d7dbcb7cf33139123390c6_types-of-it-support.webp"></div></figure><h3>Managed IT support</h3><p>If you are looking for a way to take the hassle out of managing your company's IT infrastructure, <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/fully-managed-it-support">managed IT support</a>may be the right solution for you.</p><p>With this type of IT support service, you can entrust the end-to-end management and maintenance of your IT infrastructures to a third-party vendor; This includes installing IT equipment, network monitoring, data storage, and other technical activities.</p><p>You can choose which IT functions to outsource and the service level you wish to pay for. If you're ready to take the burden off your shoulders, consider managed IT services for your business.</p><h3>Microsoft Teams support</h3><p>Since its introduction in 2016, <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/microsoft-teams-tutorials">Microsoft Teams</a>has been a game-changer for businesses worldwide.</p><p>As the world has transitioned to remote work due to the COVID-19 epidemic, Teams has enabled companies worldwide to stay connected and collaborate with their employees from a distance.</p><p>Microsoft Teams has made communication more accessible than ever, from instant messaging and video conferencing to real-time collaboration and file sharing.</p><p>With this increased reliance on Teams, businesses must have the right IT support system to handle server changes, employee training, upgrades, issues, or other problems that may arise.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/63d27e05d42196387cd5dcbd_Microsoft-office-teams.webp"></div></figure><h3>IT network support</h3><p>Having a reliable network infrastructure is essential to keeping your business secure, making Network Support one of the most vital types of IT support for your business.</p><p>At the core of this infrastructure is the IT services provider, whose job is to protect your network from internal and external threats, achieved by installing and managing firewalls, monitoring for abnormal activity, and providing 24/7 monitoring for networks with specific needs.</p><p>Your IT support will also help to set up network policies that help to protect your company, such as blocking external logins, requiring <a href="https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/topic/what-is-multifactor-authentication-e5e39437-121c-be60-d123-eda06bddf661">multi-factor authentication</a>, and more.</p><h3>Cloud services</h3><p>The 'cloud' is a term that refers to the use of the internet for storing, accessing, and sharing data and services rather than clogging up a local computer or server. Google, Amazon, IBM, and Azure all provide an essential Cloud Service.</p><p> <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/cloud-computing">The cloud</a>allows users to access their information and applications from any device with an internet connection, enabling them to work and collaborate from anywhere.</p><p>In the days of remote working, cloud services are one of the most significant types of IT support available. Naturally, businesses utilising the cloud should invest in an IT support company that can assist with all cloud requirements. Demands will involve subscriptions, updates, addressing difficulties, and direct contact with the supplier to ensure that the cloud provides the best service possible.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/63d27ee310e8ca611e4fe4e1_laptop-cloud-technology.webp"></div></figure><h3>Cyber security</h3><p>Protecting your business from cybercrime is no longer an option - it's a necessity. Every year, there are over 800,000 victims of the three most common types of cybercrime: ransomware, phishing, and malware.</p><p> <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/what-is-cybersecurity">Cyber security</a>is an essential investment that all companies should make to keep their data safe from hackers.</p><p>Invest in tough cyber security measures to protect your business. Network monitoring tools, next-gen firewalls, and anti-malware programs are all valuable tools for defending against threats.</p><p>Furthermore, engaging a reputable IT provider can bring their expertise and experience to the table, protecting against both external and insider attacks.</p><h2>Summary</h2><p>Using IT support solutions is a great way to improve efficiency and communication in a business. In the modern world, companies must ensure data security, provide quality customer service, and use the newest technology while managing their finances.</p><p>The different types of IT support solutions described here can help businesses that need help finding suitable IT solutions. Whether you need help managing your IT infrastructure, setting up Microsoft Teams, securing your network, or protecting your data, having the right IT services provider on your side is key.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/63d250ffafe8c1582a8a403b_Untitled%20(1024%20%C3%97%201024px)%20(3).png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[cybersecurity]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[What is Cybersecurity? Importance, Types, and Tools]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[what-is-cybersecurity]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60fd0]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Mar 16 2023 14:38:10 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Thu Oct 26 2023 09:18:57 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[What Is Cybersecurity? Importance, Types, and Tools!]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Cybersecurity is essential to protecting your online data. Learn about the types, importance, and tools to help you stay safe online in this informative blog.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[55]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<h2>What is cyber security, and why is it important?</h2><p>In today's world, the internet has become an indispensable part of our lives. With the rise in digital devices and internet usage, the risks associated with cyber threats have grown exponentially. Cybersecurity is a term that encompasses the techniques, technologies, and practices designed to protect our digital devices, networks, and data from unauthorised access, damage, or theft. In this blog, we will discuss the importance of cybersecurity, the role of cybersecurity professionals, the types of cybersecurity, the concept of zero trust, and the tools used in cybersecurity.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6414868a1ebc5e951374e1e5_cyber-security.webp"></div></figure><h2>What is cybersecurity?</h2><p>Cybersecurity protects digital devices, networks, and data from unauthorised access, theft, and damage. It involves implementing measures to secure computer systems, networks, and software from cyber threats, such as viruses, malware, ransomware, and other forms of cyber-attacks. Cybersecurity aims to ensure data and systems' confidentiality, integrity, and availability.</p><h3>Why is cybersecurity important?</h3><p>Cybersecurity is vital for several reasons:</p><p><strong>Protection of sensitive data:</strong>Cybersecurity measures help protect sensitive information from falling into the wrong hands. This can include personal information, financial data, and trade secrets.</p><p><strong>Business continuity:&nbsp;</strong>Cyber-attacks can lead to significant downtime, resulting in financial losses and damaging an organisation's reputation. Cybersecurity helps businesses maintain their operations and minimise the impact of a cyber-attack.</p><p><strong>Compliance with regulations:&nbsp;</strong>Organisations must comply with various cybersecurity regulations, such as the <a href="https://gdpr-info.eu/">General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)</a>, to protect user data and avoid legal penalties.</p><p><strong>National security:&nbsp;</strong>Cybersecurity is crucial for protecting critical infrastructure, such as power grids and transportation systems, from cyber-attacks that could cause widespread disruption.</p><p>Read More: <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/top-tips-for-improving-your-business-cyber-security">Improve your business cyber security</a></p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6414869c318bac0dd4f3bf8e_cyber-security-job.webp"></div></figure><h2>What does a cybersecurity professional do?</h2><p>A cybersecurity professional protects an organisation's digital assets from cyber threats. They perform various tasks, including:</p><p><strong>Risk assessment:</strong>&nbsp;Identifying vulnerabilities and potential threats to the organisation's digital assets.</p><p><strong>Implementation of security measures</strong>: Designing and deploying security solutions to protect against cyber threats.</p><p><strong>Monitoring and incident response:</strong>&nbsp;Continuously monitoring for security breaches and responding to incidents when they occur.</p><p><strong>Security training and awareness</strong>: Educating employees on best practices for maintaining cybersecurity.</p><p><strong>Compliance and regulation</strong>: Ensuring the organisation adheres to relevant cybersecurity laws and regulations.</p><h2>What are the types of cybersecurity?</h2><p>There are several types of cybersecurity, each focusing on a specific aspect of digital protection. Some of these include:</p><p><strong>Network security:</strong>&nbsp;Protecting an organisation's network infrastructure from unauthorised access and attacks.</p><p><strong>Application security:</strong>&nbsp;Ensuring the safety of software applications by identifying and fixing vulnerabilities and weaknesses.</p><p><strong>Endpoint security:</strong>&nbsp;Safeguarding endpoints, such as laptops, smartphones, and other devices, from cyber threats.</p><p><strong>Data security:</strong>&nbsp;Protecting data stored in databases and other storage systems from unauthorised access and tampering.</p><p><strong>Cloud security:</strong>&nbsp;Securing data and applications hosted on cloud platforms from cyber threats.</p><figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/641486f4fe05d2f11e5513fc_cloud-cyber-security.webp"></div></figure><h2>What is zero trust in cyber security?</h2><p>Zero Trust is a security model that assumes no user, device, or network can be trusted by default. Instead, access to resources is granted based on strict verification of the user's identity and the context in which the request is made. This model aims to minimise the risk of unauthorised access, even from within an organisation's network.</p><h2>What are the tools used in cyber security?</h2><p>There are various tools available for cybersecurity professionals to use in their efforts to protect digital assets. Some of these include:</p><h3><strong>Antivirus and anti-malware software</strong>&zwj;</h3><p>Tools designed to detect, prevent, and remove malicious software, such as viruses, worms, trojans, and ransomware.</p><h3><strong>Firewalls</strong>&zwj;</h3><p>Security systems that monitor and control incoming and outgoing network traffic based on predetermined security rules, helping to block unauthorised access to an organisation's network.</p><h3><strong>Intrusion detection and prevention systems (IDPS)</strong>&zwj;</h3><p>Tools that monitor network traffic for suspicious activity and potential threats, alerting security teams when a possible breach is detected.</p><h3><strong>Encryption tools</strong></h3><p><strong>&zwj;</strong>Software that helps protect data by converting it into an unreadable format, making it difficult for unauthorised users to access the information.</p><h3><strong>Virtual private networks (VPNs)</strong>&zwj;</h3><p>Services that create encrypted connections between users and remote networks, allowing for secure communication over the internet.</p><h3><strong>Security information and event management (SIEM) systems</strong>&zwj;</h3><p>Platforms that collect and analyse security events from various sources, providing real-time monitoring, alerts, and reports to assist in identifying and responding to potential threats.<strong>&zwj;</strong>&zwj;<strong>&zwj;</strong></p><h3><strong>Vulnerability scanners</strong>&zwj;</h3><p>Tools that scan networks, systems, and applications for security weaknesses and vulnerabilities, helping organisations identify and fix potential threats.<strong>&zwj;</strong></p><h3>&zwj;<strong>Patch management tools</strong>&zwj;</h3><p>Software solutions that help organisations identify, prioritise, and apply security updates and patches to their systems, ensuring they remain protected against known vulnerabilities.<strong>&zwj;</strong>&zwj;</p><h3>&zwj;<strong>Multi-factor authentication (MFA) solutions</strong></h3><p><strong>&zwj;</strong>Technologies that require users to provide two or more forms of identification before granting access to systems or data reduce the likelihood of unauthorised access. Security awareness training platforms tools that educate employees on best practices for maintaining cybersecurity, helping to minimise the risk of human error leading to security breaches.</p><h2>Conclusion</h2><p>Cybersecurity is an essential aspect of modern life as it helps to protect our digital devices, networks, and data from unauthorised access, damage, or theft. The field encompasses various specialised areas and requires skilled professionals to manage and secure digital assets effectively. By understanding the importance of cybersecurity, the role of<strong>cybersecurity professionals</strong>, the different types of cybersecurity, and the tools and strategies available, organisations and individuals can take proactive steps to protect themselves in the digital world.</p><p>Read More: <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/cyber-essentials-certification">Cyber Essentials Certification</a></p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6413327291875f2ba3348eba_Untitled%20(1024%20%C3%97%201024px)%20(7).png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[Cyber Security]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[it-helpdesk]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[What Is an IT Help Desk? ]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[what-is-it-help-desk]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60fd1]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Fri Mar 24 2023 13:50:16 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 17 2023 09:59:10 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[What Is an IT Help Desk? Types, Features & Importance! ]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Get the answers to your IT help desk questions with this blog. Learn about the types of help desks, key features, importance, and role of an IT help desk.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[56]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>The IT helpdesk has become essential to any organisation's IT infrastructure. As technology evolves and intertwines daily operations, businesses and institutions rely on IT help desks to provide swift and efficient solutions to technical problems. In this blog, we will discuss what an IT help desk is, its types, key features, and the importance of having one in place.</p><h2>What is an IT help desk?</h2><p>An<strong>IT help desk</strong>is a centralised resource responsible for providing technical support and assistance to end-users within an organisation. It serves as the primary point of contact for employees or customers experiencing IT-related issues, such as hardware, software, network, or other technical problems. The IT help desk ensures that technical issues are resolved quickly and efficiently, minimising downtime and allowing users to return to tasks as soon as possible. <img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/641db2698ab3d81cc044568d_remote-helpdesk-support.webp"></p><h2>What are the types of IT help desks?</h2><p>There are several types of IT help desks, each designed to cater to different organisational needs:</p><h4>Internal IT help desk</h4><p>This help desk type is dedicated to supporting an organisation's internal staff. It's usually managed by the organisation's IT department and handles employee-specific issues, such as computer troubleshooting, software installation, and network connectivity.</p><h4>External IT help desk</h4><p>An external help desk supports customers or clients of an organisation; This can involve troubleshooting product-related issues, answering technical questions, or assisting with software and hardware installations.</p><h4>Outsourced IT help desk</h4><p>Some organisations choose to outsource their IT help desk services to third-party providers. These providers specialise in handling IT support tasks and offer a range of services, from basic troubleshooting to advanced technical assistance.</p><h4>Virtual IT help desk</h4><p>Virtual help desks use remote support tools and technologies to assist in a remote location. This approach allows organisations to access IT support services from a global pool of experts and can be a cost-effective option compared to maintaining an in-house help desk team.</p><h2>What are the key features of an IT help desk?</h2><p>An effective IT help desk should possess the following features:<strong>Ticketing system:</strong>A ticketing system is crucial for tracking, prioritising, and resolving IT issues. It enables help desk agents to efficiently manage support requests and ensure that each issue is resolved on time.<strong>Knowledge base:</strong>A comprehensive knowledge base empowers help desk agents and end-users to find answers to common IT issues quickly; This can result in faster resolution times and fewer support tickets.<strong>Remote support:</strong>Providing remote support allows IT help desk agents to troubleshoot and resolve issues without being physically present at the user's location; This can save time and resources and improve response times.<strong>Automation:</strong>Automating routine tasks, such as ticket routing, escalations, and notifications, can improve the overall efficiency of the help desk and ensure that support requests are handled promptly.<strong>Reporting and analytics:</strong>Monitoring help desk performance through reporting and analytics is essential for identifying areas of improvement, measuring the effectiveness of support strategies, and optimising the help desk's overall performance. <img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/641db276b59702f9a23caa56_on-site-support.webp"></p><h2>What is the importance of an IT help desk?</h2><p><strong>The IT help desk</strong>plays a crucial role in maintaining the smooth operation of an organisation's <a href="https://www.ibm.com/topics/infrastructure">IT infrastructure</a>. Some of the key benefits include:<strong>Improved productivity:</strong>help desks minimise downtime and enable users to return to tasks quickly, increasing productivity.<strong>Enhanced customer satisfaction:</strong>A responsive and knowledgeable help desk can improve customer satisfaction by addressing their technical concerns efficiently. <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/the-importance-of-proactive-it-support"><strong>Proactive IT management</strong></a><strong>:</strong>Help desks can identify recurring issues and trends, allowing organisations to address underlying problems proactively and prevent future disruptions.</p><h2>What is the role of an IT help desk?</h2><p>An IT help desk is responsible for providing technical support and assistance to end-users within an organisation. They help diagnose, troubleshoot, and resolve many IT-related issues, including hardware malfunctions, software glitches, and network connectivity problems. The help desk's primary objective is to resolve technical issues swiftly and effectively, minimising downtime and allowing users to resume their tasks as quickly as possible.</p><h3>Key responsibilities of an IT help desk</h3><p>The responsibilities of an IT help desk can vary depending on the organisation's size, industry, and specific needs. However, some of the most common duties include the following:</p><h4>Responding to support requests</h4><p>Help desk agents are responsible for fielding user support requests through phone calls, emails, chat, or other channels. They gather necessary information, assess the issue, and provide assistance or escalate it to a higher level of support.</p><h4>Troubleshooting and problem resolution</h4><p>Help desk agents diagnose and troubleshoot a wide variety of technical issues. They use their knowledge and expertise to identify the root cause of the problem and apply appropriate solutions to resolve it.</p><h4>Hardware and software support</h4><p>The IT help desk assists users with hardware and software-related issues, such as installing or updating software, configuring hardware devices, or troubleshooting peripheral devices like printers and scanners.</p><h4>User account management</h4><p>Help desk agents manage user accounts, including setting up new accounts, resetting passwords, and assisting with access permissions.</p><h4>Network support</h4><p>They are also responsible for ensuring network connectivity and assisting users with network-related issues, such as Wi-Fi connectivity, VPN access, or email configuration.</p><h4>Maintenance and upgrades</h4><p>Help desk teams may also maintain and upgrade IT systems and infrastructure, ensuring that hardware and software components are up-to-date and functioning optimally.</p><h4>Documentation and knowledge sharing</h4><p>A crucial aspect of help desk operations is documenting solutions, creating knowledge base articles, and sharing information with other team members; This helps to ensure that the help desk operates more efficiently and can resolve issues faster. <img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/641db27e5f065c8f56614f5c_it-helpdesk-support.webp"></p><h2>Skills and qualities of an IT help desk agent</h2><p>An effective IT help desk agent should possess a range of skills and qualities, including:<strong>Technical expertise:</strong>A strong understanding of various IT systems, hardware, software, and networks is essential for diagnosing and resolving technical issues.<strong>Problem-solving skills:</strong>The ability to think critically and apply logical reasoning to troubleshoot and resolve issues is crucial for help desk agents.<strong>Communication skills:</strong>Help desk agents must communicate effectively with end-users, explaining technical concepts clearly and concisely in that is easy for non-technical users to understand.<strong>Customer service skills:</strong>Providing exceptional customer service and professionalism is crucial for ensuring user satisfaction and building trust.<strong>Patience and empathy:</strong>Help desk agents often deal with frustrated users facing technical issues. Patience and empathy are essential for understanding their concerns and providing adequate assistance.</p><h2>What is the difference between an IT help desk and an IT support?</h2><p>An IT help desk is a centralised point of contact for end-users who need assistance with technology-related issues; It primarily focuses on providing first-level support for issues such as software glitches, hardware malfunctions, and network connectivity problems. Help desks often use ticketing systems to efficiently track, prioritise, and resolve user requests. In contrast, <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/it-support">IT support</a>is a broader term encompassing a range of services to maintain and improve an organisation's IT infrastructure. It includes the help desk function but also extends to other areas, such as systems administration, network management, and IT security. IT support professionals ensure an organisation's technology infrastructure is stable, secure, and up-to-date.</p><h3>Key differences between Help desk and IT support</h3><h4><strong>Scope of services</strong></h4><p>Help desk services primarily provide immediate assistance to end-users facing technical issues. In contrast, IT support covers a broader range of responsibilities, including maintaining and optimising an organisation's IT infrastructure, managing software and hardware deployments, and ensuring IT security.</p><h4><strong>Level of expertise</strong></h4><p>Help desk agents typically handle first-level support tasks, such as troubleshooting fundamental issues and guiding users. On the other hand, IT support professionals possess a higher level of technical expertise. They may manage more complex tasks like server administration, network management, and IT security.</p><h4><strong>User interaction</strong></h4><p>Help desk professionals interact directly with end-users, assisting various channels like phone calls, emails, or chats. IT support professionals may not constantly interact with end-users directly but work behind the scenes to maintain and optimise the organisation's IT infrastructure.</p><h4><strong>Proactive vs. reactive approach</strong></h4><p>Help desk services are generally reactive, responding to issues as they arise. On the other hand, IT support takes a more proactive approach, focusing on preventing problems through regular maintenance, monitoring, and optimisation of IT systems.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/641dac1901df528e5c314b53_Untitled%20(1024%20%C3%97%201024px)%20(9).png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[phishing-attack-in-cybersecurity]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[What Is a Phishing Attack in Cyber Security, and How Can You Prevent It?]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[what-is-phishing-attack]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60fd2]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Tue Apr 04 2023 13:05:43 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 08:25:14 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[What Is Phishing Attack? | How to Prevent It | TechVertu]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Phishing attacks pose a significant threat to individuals and businesses. Learn the definition, types and how to prevent them in this blog. ]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[57]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p><strong>Phishing attacks</strong>have become increasingly common in the digital age, posing a significant threat to individuals and businesses. Understanding these attacks and how they work is essential for safeguarding your personal and organisational data. This blog will delve into phishing attacks' definition, their types, and effective measures to prevent them.</p><h2>What is a phishing attack?</h2><p>Phishing is a cyber-attack in which attackers masquerade as trustworthy entities to deceive their victims into divulging sensitive information, such as login credentials, credit card numbers, and other personal data. Typically, phishing attacks are carried out via email but can also be conducted through phone calls, text messages, and social media platforms. <img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/642c2b671db7e540f7a156e1_phishing-cyber-security.webp"></p><h2>What are the types of phishing attacks</h2><p>Here we discuss the most common types of Phishing Attacks:</p><h3><strong>Email phishing attack</strong></h3><p>This is the most common form of phishing, where attackers send fraudulent emails that appear to come from a legitimate source. The emails often contain links or attachments designed to trick recipients into revealing sensitive information or downloading malware. <a href="https://terranovasecurity.com/top-examples-of-phishing-emails/">19 Examples of Common Phishing Emails</a></p><h3><strong>Spear phishing attack</strong></h3><p>This targeted phishing is directed at specific individuals or organisations. The attackers often gather personal information about the target to make the scam appear more convincing.</p><h3><strong>Whaling</strong></h3><p>A spear phishing that targets high-level executives or other high-profile individuals within an organisation. The goal is usually to access sensitive corporate data or financial information.</p><h3><strong>Clone phishing attack</strong></h3><p>Attackers create an almost identical replica of a legitimate email the victim has previously received, modifying the content to include malicious links or attachments.</p><h3><strong>Smishing and vishing</strong></h3><p>Smishing (SMS phishing) involves sending malicious text messages. In contrast, vishing (voice phishing) involves phone calls where the attacker pretends to be a legitimate representative of a known organisation, attempting to trick the victim into sharing sensitive information. <img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/642c2b755946317a1e747904_mobile-phishing-attack.webp"></p><h2>How to prevent phishing attacks?</h2><p>There are several ways we can<strong>avoid phishing attacks</strong>:</p><h3>Educate and train:</h3><p>Provide ongoing education and training to help users recognize phishing attempts and understand the importance of not clicking on suspicious links or sharing personal information.</p><h3>Implement security software:</h3><p>Use antivirus and anti-phishing software to protect devices from malware and phishing attacks. Keep software and operating systems updated with the latest security patches.</p><h3>Use two-factor authentication (2FA):</h3><p> <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/two-factor-authentication-guide">Enable 2FA</a>for all sensitive accounts, adding an extra layer of protection beyond just a password.</p><h3>Be wary of unsolicited emails:</h3><p>Approach any unsolicited email cautiously, mainly if it contains links or attachments. Verify the sender's email address, and contact the purported sender through a separate, trusted channel if necessary.</p><h3>Hover over links:</h3><p>Hover the mouse cursor over a link to reveal the destination URL without clicking. Do not click on the link if the URL looks suspicious or does not match the expected destination.</p><h3>Verify requests for sensitive information:</h3><p>If you receive a request for sensitive information, always verify the authenticity of the proposal through alternative means before sharing any details.</p><h3>Report phishing attempts:</h3><p>Notify your IT department or relevant security authority about any phishing attempts, so they can take appropriate action to protect others. <img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/642c2b7f4f96d40b167973ce_cyber-security-attack.webp"></p><h3>Conclusion</h3><p>Phishing attacks are a significant threat to <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/what-is-cybersecurity">cyber security</a>. By understanding the different types of attacks and implementing the prevention measures discussed in this blog, you can better protect yourself and your organisation from falling victim to these scams. Stay vigilant, and always prioritise your digital safety.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/642c23ffd16e0a48f7d67bd2_Untitled%20(1024%20%C3%97%201024px)%20(10).png]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/642c23ffd16e0a48f7d67bd2_Untitled%20(1024%20%C3%97%201024px)%20(10).png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[Cyber Security]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[update-adobe-flash-today]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[Why You Should Update Adobe Flash Today]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[why-you-should-update-adobe-flash-today]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60ddd]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:01 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Thu Oct 12 2023 15:21:30 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Why You Should Update Adobe Flash Today?]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Adobe Flash is a platform that is used for many websites to create rich dynamic content; But It's crucial to keep Adobe Flash up to date.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[18]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<figure><div><img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b2d1344b38e25eb0962b_Adobe-flash.png"></div></figure><p>Adobe Flash is a multimedia platform which combines graphics, animation, video and sound. It is used for many websites to create rich dynamic content. However, hackers have always been known to exploit weaknesses in the security of Adobe Flash and use those to compromise systems. And now that Adobe Flash is embedded into Windows 10 and into browsers such as Chrome, it is more important than ever to protect against hackers using this to gain access to your data and infect your machine with malware.</p><p>One such weakness was revealed this week by cyber criminals and was first noticed by security researchers when a clinic, which provides medical and cosmetic services to high level employees of the Russian government, was targeted with a 0day exploit.</p><h2>&zwj;<strong>What is a 0-day exploit?</strong></h2><p><strong>&zwj;</strong>This is a security weakness in software which is not yet known or patched by the developers of the software. Bug bounty deals are often offered by developers of leading software to security researchers who find and report bugs. This usually allows those bugs to be fixed before hackers can use them. But exploits of this kind are also commonly sold on the black market, sometimes for very high sums. Having a tool like this, which has not yet had any patches developed, is powerful and can be used for targeted attacks like the one in the clinic.</p><p>Adobe have responded quickly to the news and have already released a patch in version 32.0.0.101 of Flash Player which protects against this exploit. It received the nickname &ldquo;Operation Poison Needles&rdquo; due to the location it was initially discovered. However, now that this has been disclosed publicly, many other reports of hackers using this same exploit to spread ransomware have come to light.</p><p>This malicious adobe flash code is often embedded into a regular word document. However, when you open it, it will prompt you to enable the malicious Adobe flash content. If you do so, your machine will be infected.</p><p>You can go to <a href="https://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/end-of-life-alternative.html">https://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/end-of-life-alternative.html</a>to download the latest updates to Adobe Flash.</p><p>You can always give our team a call and let us handle security updates like the above for you automatically. With our remote agent software we can ensure all of your systems are always kept up to date and protected against the latest generation of cyber threats.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a30ff187f654f3ebfcde16_flash-warning.jpg]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a30ff187f654f3ebfcde16_flash-warning.jpg]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[windows11-vs-windows-365-difference]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[Windows 11 vs Windows 365: What's The Difference?]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[windows-11-vs-windows-365-whats-the-difference]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60ebc]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:12 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 08:51:19 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Sun Nov 19 2023 11:04:06 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[Windows 11 vs Windows 365: What are The Differences?]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Everyone can buy and use windows 11 on their systems, while Windows 365 is a subscription service that takes the operating system to the cloud.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[50]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>Microsoft announced the release of Windows 11 at the end of June. Only weeks later, they followed with a surprise introduction of Windows 365, a subscription service that takes the operating system to the cloud. It is designed for businesses, with IT managers and the new hybrid working era in mind. In this article, we will go through the features and benefits of both and explain the differences between the two.</p><h2><strong>What is Windows 11?</strong></h2><p> <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-gb/windows/windows-11">Windows 11</a>is the latest version of Windows operating system. After 6 years of the same user interface, the successor of Windows 10 has undergone a complete makeover, launching a fresher, more minimalist style than its precursors. Microsoft describes Windows 11 as a "calm and creative space" that "brings you closer to the people and things you love." Over the last 15 months, our devices have often been the only place where we can work, connect, play, be entertained and stay informed. Undoubtedly, this has influenced Microsoft's goal of making these areas intuitive and easy to switch between. <img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b349344b38456cb0981d_MicrosoftTeams-image-1024x576.png"> Photo credit (Microsoft) - https://news.microsoft.com/june-24-2021/</p><h3><strong>New features for Windows 11</strong></h3><p>- The start menu has been refreshed and opens now from the centre of the taskbar. - Live tiles have gone, but are replaced by widgets for things like news, weather, and calendar events. - The addition of desktops helps you stay organised and focused by creating separate, customisable desktops for every part of your life. - Snap Layouts allows you to open multiple Windows simultaneously in your chosen layout, adapt to the size of your screen, while Snap Groups remembers collections of apps you have used and keeps them for you so you can return to them later. - Microsoft Teams is built into Windows 11 devices, so you can connect directly to your contacts from your desktop. - Vertical tabs make it easier to find what you are looking for, so you don't get lost in several tabs. - Updates are 40% smaller and occur in the background for fewer interruptions. No specific release date has been confirmed, but Microsoft said it will arrive during the 2021 holiday season. However, it is expected that this only refers to the date at which new laptops and PCs with Windows 11 pre-installed will be available to buy. Users who want to upgrade their existing Windows devices are likely to have to wait until 2022.</p><h2><strong>What is Windows 365?</strong></h2><p>Windows 365 is a cloud-based operating system. It&rsquo;s the latest service offering from Microsoft, which is referred to as a &lsquo;Cloud PC&rsquo;. It "combines the power and security of the cloud with the versatility of the PC" and allows employees to access their desktop virtually, rather than rely on a physical device. Influenced by the colossal change in our relationships with work and technology caused by the pandemic, Windows 365 has been created exclusively for companies to make hybrid work easier and more productive. The service reduces the security risks associated with working from home or using personal devices, as information is stored in the cloud, not on the device itself. Read More: <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/windows-365-in-the-cloud">Windows 365 main features that help organisations</a></p><h3><strong>What is a Cloud PC: How Windows 365 works</strong></h3><p>Windows 365 is used and appears in the same way as the traditional Windows operating system, but is accessed and managed via your Internet browser or the Microsoft Remote Desktop app. Your entire desktop is stored in a secure data centre, not on your actual device. Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella said the following in a recent statement: "Just as applications have been brought to the cloud with software-as-a-Service, we are now bringing the operating system to the cloud, giving organisations greater flexibility and a secure way to enable their workforce to be more productive and connected, regardless of location".</p><h2><strong>What is the difference between Windows 365 and Windows 11?</strong></h2><p>The main difference between the two is that Windows 11 is a traditional operating system that anyone can buy and install on their computer, while Windows 365 is a subscription service that allows companies to stream Windows 11 (or Windows 10) from the cloud to any device.</p><h3><strong>Key differences:</strong></h3><p>- A traditional operating system like Windows 11 is installed on your device and consumes RAM and storage space. Windows 365, on the other hand, does not take up any space on your device, as everything is stored in the cloud, but it means an Internet connection is required to run it. - Windows 10 and 11 are either pre-installed on devices or you buy a licence, and it's yours to keep forever. Windows 365, on the other hand, operates on a subscription model, so you rent your desktops essentially. This could prove useful if you hire freelancers or temporary workers, as you can quickly set up their new cloud PC and secure access to company data without the need to make long-term investments.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1c7d2754c655932d73f16_Windows-11-1-1024x1024.png]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1c7d2754c655932d73f16_Windows-11-1-1024x1024.png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
	<node>
		<imagefilename><![CDATA[windows-365-in-the-cloud]]></imagefilename>
		<title><![CDATA[Windows 365: In the Cloud]]></title>
		<slug><![CDATA[windows-365-in-the-cloud]]></slug>
		<collectionid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60d7a]]></collectionid>
		<itemid><![CDATA[653f54bf85c491c573b60e29]]></itemid>
		<createdon><![CDATA[Thu Jun 09 2022 09:08:10 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></createdon>
		<updatedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 17 2023 11:50:15 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></updatedon>
		<publishedon><![CDATA[Tue Oct 31 2023 08:05:46 GMT+0000 (Coordinated Universal Time)]]></publishedon>
		<metatitle><![CDATA[How can Windows 365 help businesses?]]></metatitle>
		<metadescription><![CDATA[Windows 365 provides businesses of all sizes with a new way of experiencing Windows from the cloud to any device that is easy to use.]]></metadescription>
		<customsortorder><![CDATA[46]]></customsortorder>
		<postbody><![CDATA[<p>Microsoft brings Windows 10 and 11 to the cloud with the recently announced <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-gb/windows-365"><strong>Windows 365</strong></a>. The service will provide businesses of all sizes a new way of experiencing Windows, promising a personalised PC experience from the cloud to any device that is easy to use and just as effortless for IT to manage.</p><h2>How can Windows 365 help your business?</h2><p>The pandemic caused a new way of working for thousands across the globe, transformed by virtual processes and remote collaboration. Microsoft is capitalising on the power of the cloud with Window 365, strongly aimed at business users who have transitioned to a hybrid workforce to elevate the workplace experience. Hybrid work has fundamentally changed the role of technology in organisations today, said Jared Spataro, corporate vice president, <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/microsoft-office-365"><strong>Microsoft 365</strong></a>. With workforces more disparate than ever before, organisations need a new way to deliver a great productivity experience with increased versatility, simplicity and security. Cloud PC is an exciting new category of hybrid personal computing that turns any device into a personalised, productive, and secure digital workspace. The announcement of Windows 365 is just the beginning of what will be possible as we blur the lines between the device and the cloud. <img src="https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/6284b342d4feec918de713c0_Microsoft-365-In-the-Cloud.jpeg"></p><h2><strong>3 ways Windows 365 will help any organisation</strong></h2><h3><strong>Flexibility:</strong></h3><p>With instant-on boot to their personal Cloud PC, users can stream all their applications, tools, data, and settings from the cloud across any device. Windows 365 will provide the full PC experience in the cloud. The cloud also brings versatility in processing both power and storage, enabling IT to either scale up or down based on their needs, with a choice of either Windows 10 or 11 (once Windows 11 becomes available later this year).</p><h3><strong>Simplicity:</strong></h3><p>With a Cloud PC, users can effortlessly log in and pick back up straight where they left off across devices, providing a straightforward and familiar Windows experience delivered by the cloud. For IT, Windows 365 also provides simplification of deployment, updates, and management.</p><h3><strong>Security:</strong></h3><p>Microsoft claims that Windows 365 is secure by design, leveraging not only the power of the cloud but the principles of <a href="https://www.techvertu.co.uk/blog/what-is-cybersecurity#:~:text=What%20is%20zero%20trust%20in%20cyber%20security%3F">Zero Trust</a>. Information is securely stored in the cloud, not on a device. Microsoft will reveal Windows 365 pricing when the service becomes generally available on August 2, 2021.</p>]]></postbody>
		<postsummary><![CDATA[]]></postsummary>
		<mainimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1cdb1754c655fb5d76ef9_Windows%20365%20.png]]></mainimage>
		<thumbnailimage><![CDATA[https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/610dfb67e987d82fadc6776c/62a1cdb1754c655fb5d76ef9_Windows%20365%20.png]]></thumbnailimage>
		<featured><![CDATA[TRUE]]></featured>
		<category><![CDATA[IT Support]]></category>
		<gallery><![CDATA[]]></gallery>
		<gallery2><![CDATA[]]></gallery2>
		<gallery3><![CDATA[]]></gallery3>
		<gallery4><![CDATA[]]></gallery4>
		<g5><![CDATA[]]></g5>
		<g6><![CDATA[]]></g6>
		<g7><![CDATA[]]></g7>
		<g8><![CDATA[]]></g8>
		<g9><![CDATA[]]></g9>
		<g10><![CDATA[]]></g10>
		<g11><![CDATA[]]></g11>
		<g12><![CDATA[]]></g12>
		<g13><![CDATA[]]></g13>
		<g14><![CDATA[]]></g14>
		<g15><![CDATA[]]></g15>
		<g16><![CDATA[]]></g16>
		<g17><![CDATA[]]></g17>
		<g18><![CDATA[]]></g18>
		<g19><![CDATA[]]></g19>
		<g20><![CDATA[]]></g20>
	</node>
</data>
